{"_id":{"$oid":"5d0b22060bde880017a672e6"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561010694665"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561010694665"},"name":"Ashwini Kamalesh","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"We had overview session by Sowmya for Validation team."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Got an overview of the ASPICE.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d0b68dfe868d30017988c64"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561028831209"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561028831209"},"name":"Sasi Kiran Vanapalli","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Context setting and scope","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Almost covered as per the scope","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1.5 Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Yet to use the product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, Day 2 is a bit slow due to complex topics but overall it is good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d0bb89b09585e0017b5d387"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561049243391"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561049243391"},"name":"Divya Chandra","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Aspice content though looks simple but in reality it is confusing and takes time to settle down. L1, L2 , L3 concept repition throughtout the training was helpful."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Difference between different levels of Aspice.  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Mostly covered everything. Coverage of topics was relevant and good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":"scope of applying currently is the biggest challenge with EB India. "},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"There was lot of efforts put in to get all the information and flow together for this training. Thanks to the entire Quality team.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d11a38a490a580017338156"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561437066603"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561437066603"},"name":"","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"2","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"4"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d11a5af490a580017338157"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561437615423"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561437615423"},"name":"Rasna","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Came to know in which level our project stands"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Got an overview about ASPICE standards and levels","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better if Level 4 and level 5 are explained more in detailed","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Currently not using any EB product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d11b4fc93ce7900177d6769"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561441532146"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561441532146"},"name":"","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the way the learnings were imparted and co-related through the activities"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Introduction and management section","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Yet to start using ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d11eff7e1e3280017969973"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561456631002"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561456631002"},"name":"","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Got complete ASPICE overview "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ASPICE  levels ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Most of  the thing are covered ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"User experience","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37d809a448170017a2fd7a"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563940873103"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563940873103"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Information"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercise","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Diagnostics (DCM, DEM in depth), component configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"MCAL","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Well satisfied. We expect training on other topics for more details. Thank you!","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37d8b6a448170017a2fd7b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941046147"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941046147"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"No enough time, 3 day seems like not enough to understand every"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"OS, Comstack, Overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not yet","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For Powertrain","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37d91aa448170017a2fd7c"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941146463"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941146463"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"New","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37d9cfa448170017a2fd7d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941327365"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941327365"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"I was unable to do most of the exercises due to PC/tool performance issues"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Partially (Met expectations)"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Understanding the structure/layers","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not worked yet","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37dc41a448170017a2fd7f"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941953064"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941953064"},"name":"Shoaib Ahmed Khan","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Exercises"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Mode management & memory stack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"COM & OBD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37f7b4a493710017089078"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563948980613"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563948980613"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM stack hands on session","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"It would be goodif you can explain more examples during theory sessions","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For COM stack configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"-Basic information of different autosar layers\n-Com stack\n-SWC concepts\n- Hands-on on SWC\n- Gained some knowledge in the above","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37f7b4a493710017089079"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563948980787"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563948980787"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM stack hands on session","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"It would be goodif you can explain more examples during theory sessions","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For COM stack configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"-Basic information of different autosar layers\n-Com stack\n-SWC concepts\n- Hands-on on SWC\n- Gained some knowledge in the above","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37f9bda49371001708907a"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563949501248"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563949501248"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Explaination of our doubts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Theory & practicals","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good Training","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37fa31a49371001708907b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563949617856"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563949617856"},"name":"Surabhi","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Config, Com Stack, Diag Stack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Safety Library","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes :)","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d381bc3f9f98f00177bf65c"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958211269"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958211269"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Safety, diagnostics"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Config, Com","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Six months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"CDD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, well experienced trainers and organised training","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d381c25f9f98f00177bf65d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958309711"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958309711"},"name":"Yogesh Patel","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Exercises"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM stack ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Autosar, CDD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. It was really good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d381e8bf9f98f00177bf65e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958923257"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958923257"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"It is good"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"One who dont know the subject, understanding might be difficult"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Autosar","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It is good with theoritical. Practically, it is difficult to understand.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d3968ead5417000174fc60b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1564043498842"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1564043498842"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation was very clear to understand"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"presentation & practical session;","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"YES, I am new to AUTOSAR, it was clear understanding for me.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d4c04bcb5f7dd0017da810d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1565263036182"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1565263036182"},"name":"Manish Kumar","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"TDD approach to write the implementation code."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"TDD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I don't know","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"implementation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"YES","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d4cdf7ea1e6c70017775582"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1565319038414"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1565319038414"},"name":"","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Yes, as I learnt a new approach on how to program"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The difference between writing a code directly and using the TDD approach and then writing the code.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, I am satisfied with the training and looking forward to attend more of such sessions.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d4d16479bc80d0017f73ef4"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1565333063565"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1565333063565"},"name":"Raksha Rao Karaya","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The concept of thinking from Testers perspective is a new concept. Even though its tough, its good to make it a practice"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The hands-on training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More examples","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d4d31fc08a435001794931e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1565340156977"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1565340156977"},"name":"Raksha Rao Karaya","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Collaborating with people from different teams"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Thinking when contraints are produced","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Discuss the right way to solve the given problem","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"The training was very good..The idea of TDD was not known to me and the concept is really good and will be useful during lifetime.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d4d33d908a435001794931f"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1565340633052"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1565340633052"},"name":"Mohana Kumaran T","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Training has completely changed my way of approach in developing a functionality. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Interaction during exercises.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Very much. Kudos to Rene Fuger!","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d4d37c908a4350017949320"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1565341641169"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1565341641169"},"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Without pressure, handling the problems towards solution with TDD"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"same issue with different approach.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"every section, trainer can also share the info regarding, what are the possibilities to achieve the constraints.  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"5 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Integration tests of project. while writing the test cases , I could think with more clarity. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes I have satisfied with the training , I got the TDD model of work and  approach. And dealing with different coding language partner will make the new languages known.\nplease if possible , end of every session share, how to overcome the constraints. \nthanks.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d4d48cc08a4350017949321"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1565345996338"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1565345996338"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Writing programming with different-different conditions"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Requirement understanding part","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No idea","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Tresos tooling","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"YES","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d4d59e3c6670800178b169d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1565350371931"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1565350371931"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"More practical lessons, rather than theoritical"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The workshop","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Theoritical explanantion on TDD concept","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Event was too casual in nature. We could have arranged some memorable like certificate, memento etc for the participants.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d4d59e5c6670800178b169e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1565350373481"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1565350373481"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"More practical lessons, rather than theoritical"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The workshop","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Theoritical explanantion on TDD concept","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Event was too casual in nature. We could have arranged some memorable like certificate, memento etc for the participants.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d50e22a522ca300176ea9bd"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1565581866002"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1565581866002"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Knowing about a new SW development method is what I liked and the introduction to it was explanatory enough."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The workshop one day before the event to know about TDD was helpful","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It was a good learning experience about TDD and working with different partner for every round was an excellent idea.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5e55fe016e8a00172d6d53"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566463486792"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566463486792"},"name":"","training":"TDD Workshop 02","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Helped me in leaning of writting code with better readiliblity. learned about how to optimize code"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Learning Code optimization ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Don't thik of anytopic as of now","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"infotainment","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It was a good learning  experience","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5e58a4016e8a00172d6d54"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566464164605"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566464164605"},"name":"","training":"TDD Workshop 02","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"i liked the approach. easy to understand with examples and step by step execution"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"simple comprehensive coding approach","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none that i am aware of","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"product design","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"i enjoyed the training as i have been made aware of a new type of coding technique that helps both the programmer and anyone else to understand it at a later date.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f6cc2e5f4ca0017874212"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566534850432"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566534850432"},"name":"SANJAYA KUMAR PANDA","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Approach to TDD was really good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"TDD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"How to deal with TDD in support or maintenance project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"8 Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Adaptive AUTOSAR","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, Would like to thank to all organizers to conduct such training in India","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f6d2be5f4ca0017874213"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566534955957"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566534955957"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"None"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"code practice","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f6d7be5f4ca0017874214"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566535035103"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566535035103"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Workshop","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"How to apply in the product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f6f13e5f4ca0017874215"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566535443462"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566535443462"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes. With some improvement in content ( more specific to Audience) this training can be very useful.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f6f42e5f4ca0017874216"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566535490728"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566535490728"},"name":"","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f6f8ae5f4ca0017874217"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566535562287"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566535562287"},"name":"SAMBIT PATNAIK","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"TDD aproach for development"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"TDD and refactor","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"8 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"PoC","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"More such trainings to be conducted that lets one think out of the usual day to day schedules.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f72d3e5f4ca0017874218"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566536403117"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566536403117"},"name":"","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"The example task was good for beginners."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":"The exercise was simple, but using TDD with constraints was interesting and challenging."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"Well presented and methodical approach...kudos!!","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"Gelled along excellently with the participants, those short discussions were thought provoking.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The stuctured approach and introduction of new constraints kept me guessing and helped understand and participate throught out the day."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Those one-on-one discussions at the desk, on how to use TDD with constraints>","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"may be much more discussions post each constraint, on ways to approach the problem. But we do understand that it was difficult to do in a one-day workshop.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"8 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Generation of Classic Autosar Stack.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"Thanks to the organizers for the preparatory sessions and the during the actual session as well...."},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":"Currently looking for ways on how to apply it in day to day work."},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"It was new and interesting."}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes and looking forward to attend more such workshops.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f7657e5f4ca0017874219"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566537303309"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566537303309"},"name":"SANJAYA K PANDA","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Approach to TDD was really good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"TDD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"How to deal with TDD in support or maintenance project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"8 Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Adaptive AUTOSAR","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f7730e5f4ca001787421a"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566537520204"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566537520204"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The way it was organized"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"learning about test cases","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More emphasis on writing test cases than actual coding logic.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f7e0fe5f4ca001787421e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566539279692"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566539279692"},"name":"Zaid Imroz","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The idea that test cases do not explode exponentially with the evolution of the system is a great advantage."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The test first and write next approach.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"How the overall architecture e.g. MVC, MVVM, SOA etc. fit in the picture of TDD.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not really an EB Product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"I don't know what this field means in this context.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, the training was like a journey that starts at the \"Destination\" and ends at the \"Beginning\".","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f892de5f4ca001787421f"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566542125961"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566542125961"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Liked the approach which is really important to produce a good quality software."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Different various sessions planned which was interesting and made us to think.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Advanced Unit Test topics can be useful. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not worked","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For every new project in the initial development stage we can adopt this approach.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes the training was very good and useful. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f9a7296632300178e287e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566546546818"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566546546818"},"name":"Tarun Trivedi","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The different contarinst intoduced during the different levels."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Working with people having knowledge of different domains and different programming languages.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"As it was new to me so Idon't think so anyth","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Ya It was a good experience to attend the session, as a suggestion I would suggest the alloted time should be more for the event.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f9a7496632300178e287f"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566546548102"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566546548102"},"name":"Tarun Trivedi","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The different contarinst intoduced during the different levels."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Working with people having knowledge of different domains and different programming languages.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"As it was new to me so Idon't think so anyth","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Ya It was a good experience to attend the session, as a suggestion I would suggest the alloted time should be more for the event.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d5f9c7496632300178e2880"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566547060969"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566547060969"},"name":"Tarun Trivedi","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The way in which presenter shared the information with us."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I get introduced to the new approach of coding i.e. TDD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"It was a new approach for me so don't know much a","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes I was satisfied by the training. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d635c1dae828f001754db01"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566792733216"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566792733216"},"name":"","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Simple exercises taken up to explain the topic"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Unit test","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Applicability in project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Do not use Unit test in my project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, overall good training experience","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d635c77ae828f001754db02"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566792823541"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566792823541"},"name":"","training":"TDD Workshop 02","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked overall knowledge of the presenter regarding the topic of presentation "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Examples to justify the explanation.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not worked on the topic before.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Presently None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d635faaae828f001754db03"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566793641999"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566793641999"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"TDD"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Coding","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Work on projects","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d636063ae828f001754db04"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566793827161"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566793827161"},"name":"Indrayani","training":"TDD Workshop 02","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Developing code depending depending on the use case. Development is time consuming but less error pron."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Undertanding TDD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Not enough time was available for covering unit test for legacy code","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It was a good session overall. We understood the approach of test driven development. I feel its more useful for projects in development phase than bug fixing. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d6362f3ae828f001754db05"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566794483860"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566794483860"},"name":"Syed Abrar Hussaini","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Yes, I am excited to apply this in my application development environment."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The changing constraints in every session forced to look at the problem with a different perspective. No pressure of completing the task helped in learning more.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Application development.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. I am satisfied with the training. The changing constraints in every session forced to look at the problem with a different perspective. No pressure of completing the task helped in learning more.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d636886ae828f001754db06"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566795910669"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566795910669"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"TTD approach"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Each rounds were interesting with contraints","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1.6years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"EB guide plugin development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Overall event was organized very well, Got to know how and where to use TTD. Each round with some rules were amazing, which made us to think and try something new which we never did in our daily work.\nThank you.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d636912ae828f001754db07"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566796050584"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566796050584"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Interaction with different people and knowing different coding styles."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Knowledge sharing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Final solution for the problem given","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"15 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"writing test cases","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d636955ae828f001754db08"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566796117954"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566796117954"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"TTD approach"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Each rounds were interesting with contraints","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1.6years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"EB guide plugin development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Got to know about how to write TDD.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d636b57ae828f001754db09"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566796631932"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566796631932"},"name":"","training":"TDD Workshop 02","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Writing the Unit test case before actual implementation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Writing the Unit test case before actual implementation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Example is very basic. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes, it's good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d6376c6ae828f001754db0a"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566799558949"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566799558949"},"name":"","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Sessions was more like for freshers not for experienced people"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"workshop","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nothing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"not worked on product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Don't have idea on this.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It was good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d637f91ae828f001754db0c"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566801809654"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566801809654"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The trainer has good expertise over the TDD, his presentation was good."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercises are very good able to code the samething with different approaches.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Post analysis of the exercises.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 Year 4 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d637f98ae828f001754db0d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566801816263"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566801816263"},"name":"","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The trainer has good expertise over the TDD, his presentation was good."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Knowing about designing the code using the TDD.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Training could have been more interactive.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year 4 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d63a4562c96c9001709237b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566811222141"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566811222141"},"name":"Priya Verma","training":"TDD Workshop 02","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"Exercises were not included as a part of training."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"It was a opportunity to learn something new, which would be useful in future. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"New topic to learn, so it was overall good learning opportunity.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not yet.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"It was not product specific training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, It was good. Learned something new apart from daily routine.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d63b3a22c96c90017092381"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566815138412"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566815138412"},"name":"","training":"LearnLab : Coderetreat","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":" "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d63b3e62c96c90017092382"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566815206646"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566815206646"},"name":"","training":"TDD workshop","trainers":"Rene Fuger","location":"EB India","date":"2019-08-07","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Rene Fuger","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":" "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":"Food can have a variety"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d6628ee44e69d0017bab1f2"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976238590"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976238590"},"name":"Alwyn Antony","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation is good. In the Training. Consider people Don't have knowledge on autosar concept also. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Presentation ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More content about overview of Autosar ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not worked ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"planning to use it in Integration ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training is very good for Who all have prior knowledge on EB Tressos","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d66294f44e69d0017bab1f3"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976335299"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976335299"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"No"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"OS and RTE configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Diagnostic","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d66296544e69d0017bab1f4"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976357060"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976357060"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberDouble":"4.333333333333333"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberDouble":"4.666666666666667"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"COM configuration"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"General configuration part for all modules","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 Years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"DEM and COM","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Actually order of training, like module order 1st COM then DCM and DEM like that.  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d66297d44e69d0017bab1f5"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976381610"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976381610"},"name":"Shailender Chauhan","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberDouble":"4.333333333333333"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Intercative sessions . "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Os stack config and its hands On examples","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Some basics for every module before going in details","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For RTE generation ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes .","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d6629b544e69d0017bab1f6"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976437024"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976437024"},"name":"Ajeet Singh Saini","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberDouble":"4.333333333333333"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Need more explanation regarding BswM and EcuM , ComM  "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"to configuration and generation of the file using tools ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"IoHwAb ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"weekly","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"configuration check  and modification ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"OK","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d6629c544e69d0017bab1f7"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976453795"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976453795"},"name":"Tapas Dey","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The training was comprehensive containing the understanding of Autosar development flow using EB."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands-on traininig was the most valuable part which complimented the understanding required for the training. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Artext related knowledge could have been shared. We were dependable on other tools for the system extract.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW configurations","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training met the expectations by large. Some topics of the training were little fast.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d6629cd44e69d0017bab1f8"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976461094"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976461094"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"Topics like DEM/DCM where unknown to some participants so maybe a basic beginners introduction could have be provided. Just doing the configuration and not knowing the usecases is not fun."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Was hoping more autosar was told than how to do in tresos. But it was interesting to know lot of options that would reduce the manual effort"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Tool usuage ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"some real time use cases ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1yr","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Basic Software ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Happy I attended the training. learnt about COM which was new to me. Thank you for your time. Appreciate your knowledge sharing.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d662a1944e69d0017bab1f9"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976537434"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976537434"},"name":"SAMEER SAXENA","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"OS ,COM module"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Technical Interaction","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More time could be spent on diagnostics module","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Body and Security project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Satisfied with the training ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d662a3a44e69d0017bab1fa"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976570593"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976570593"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"There were lot of modules covered for configuration. May be more tailored to suit module wise."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuration on all the modules","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More options in tool specific to modules. May be the pace would have been bit slower","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":" beginner in EB tresos","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"RTE","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Neutral mode.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d662a5644e69d0017bab1fb"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976598804"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976598804"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Seems to be fast walkthrough of the modules, Need to explore all the options in the Tressos tool.Need more theoratical explanations before the practical sessions,Need correlation between the autosar concept and the EB tressos configuration"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Better interaction and clarifying doubts","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exploring all possible options for configuring modules in tressos","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"RTE generation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training is satisfactory ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d662a5744e69d0017bab1fc"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976599100"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976599100"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Seems to be fast walkthrough of the modules, Need to explore all the options in the Tressos tool.Need more theoratical explanations before the practical sessions,Need correlation between the autosar concept and the EB tressos configuration"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Better interaction and clarifying doubts","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exploring all possible options for configuring modules in tressos","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"RTE generation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training is satisfactory ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d662a8344e69d0017bab1fd"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976643523"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976643523"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.3333333333333335"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberDouble":"4.333333333333333"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":" It covered the basic configuration parameters"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"OS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"IPDUM, WDGM and IO modules","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 Years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"COM and Diag modules","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training covered the agenda but the coverage of advanced topics like E2E, PNC, Crypto and Safety topics will be more helpful","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d662ab544e69d0017bab1fe"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976693782"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1566976693782"},"name":"Plaban Kumar Behera","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental BU B&S","date":"2019-08-26 to 2019-08-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.6666666666666665"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberDouble":"4.333333333333333"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Overall information for general configuration is covered & we all participants can generate project"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Com, Mode Management","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Ethernet & LIN ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"configuration of com stack for CAN LIN Ethernet","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f633caa01e00173b2f3e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749683920"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749683920"},"name":"Nikitha Kiran","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Everything was so inspiring and well organised"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"EB products and innovation and technology","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nothing as such","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes completely","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f657caa01e00173b2f3f"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749719940"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749719940"},"name":"PARAS KUMAR","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Trainers experience to provide the relevant information."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Individual topics had their own role/information.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f6adcaa01e00173b2f40"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749805201"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749805201"},"name":"Manjunathan G","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"understood complete organization structure"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"HR policies","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f6b6caa01e00173b2f41"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749814021"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749814021"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Some of the sessions were not taken. Products overview was really good. The presenter has good knowledge."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Products Overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Finance, Projects Overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Good way of knowing the organization.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f6d7caa01e00173b2f42"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749847962"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749847962"},"name":"MADHUSUDHAN A S","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Got to know about different types of EB products"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"vision and mission ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"EB tresos -1.6 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"MCAL configuration ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"YES","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f70acaa01e00173b2f43"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749898554"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749898554"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Products Overview,POSH,IT Overview are good.Quality is more abstract and not able to relate"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Products Overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Finance","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.Training gave an overall idea about EB\nFew Planned Session did not happen due to non-availability of trainer\nIt would be good if those sessions are re-planned","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f712caa01e00173b2f44"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749906090"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749906090"},"name":"Manikandan S M","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Trainers are open for any question and extrovert"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"QMS and Product overview to understand the company's Goal , Mission","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It was a Well planned to make new comers to understand the EB nature and culture.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f73acaa01e00173b2f45"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749946138"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749946138"},"name":"Meghana Sambranikar","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the way the presenter interacted with the participants in a simple and understandable manner."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Understanding the core policies and processes of the company ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Project overview and Finance overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes I am satisfied with the training and all the information given which will definitely help me in getting acquainted with the processes of the company at a much faster pace. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f73acaa01e00173b2f46"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749946912"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749946912"},"name":"Madhunita","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Content about EB each division info provided "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"HR - discussion with omkar, Over all information about EB projects and products","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 weeks","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f73bcaa01e00173b2f47"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749947075"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749947075"},"name":"Madhunita","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Content about EB each division info provided "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"HR - discussion with omkar, Over all information about EB projects and products","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 weeks","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f73bcaa01e00173b2f48"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749947487"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749947487"},"name":"Madhunita","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Content about EB each division info provided "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"HR - discussion with omkar, Over all information about EB projects and products","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 weeks","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f753caa01e00173b2f49"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749971950"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567749971950"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Good interaction and understanding of policies"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"HR policies, peoplestrong tool and infohub","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Pregnancy policy, Role of leaders in the organization, awards and recognition","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Project activities","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training must be done proactively. Some trainers did not turn up and the content lacked lot of information. There was very less excitement in welcoming the new folks.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f773caa01e00173b2f4a"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567750003760"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567750003760"},"name":"Amarnath K","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Corporate overview & Products overview"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"HR Overview & Data protection","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Finance ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not applicable","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Not applicable","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Thank you for the induction and efforts ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f783caa01e00173b2f4b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567750019436"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567750019436"},"name":"Ipsita Das","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The information provided and the  patience showcased by the presenters in handling the induction"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Infomation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"two days","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For application of leave, holiday details, personal infomation update and trainings","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"I am satisfied with the training and thanks for the great induction","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f799caa01e00173b2f4c"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567750041059"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567750041059"},"name":"Abhinav Singh","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Every session helped me understand the values of the company and love the way things are organised here"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Product and Innovation, Employee policy","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not applicable","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Not applicable","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, satisfied with it","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f7dfcaa01e00173b2f4d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567750111909"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567750111909"},"name":"Gopinath G","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"it was informative about EB India"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Session by sanjay was very much useful to know products where EB india is working on","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Project related topics  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good to know on the products our company working, which will be help on planning our career growth.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d71f8f4caa01e00173b2f4e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567750388166"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567750388166"},"name":"Hari kiran L","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"information provided is comprehensive and helpful"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Getting to know more about the various projects EB is working on across different branches","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None that i can think of","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Technical work, time logs","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"The information provided during the induction was comprehesible and useful to me as an employee. It is also useful to get to know ind etails about various projects EB is working on and all the facilities EB provide to enchance Employee work experince.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d722b78ec6eb00017a18440"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567763320076"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567763320076"},"name":"shivayya Gadag","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti Osram","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"Sivaram =5, Lokesh=3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":"Sivaram=4, Lokesh=3"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"Sivaram=4, Lokesh=3"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"Sivaram=4, Lokesh=3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"RTE and NVM","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Autosar BSW configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes .","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d722e74ec6eb00017a18441"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567764084591"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567764084591"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti Osram","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberDouble":"4.5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"include in depth details for each module during training"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"OS, RTE and Comstack related topics","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Indepth training on comM module and CanNm","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Comstack, Nm, ComM, BswM, Nvm and RTE configurations","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"The training time could have been longer for discussing concepts in depth.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d72364aec6eb00017a18442"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567766090233"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567766090233"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti Osram","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"handson session is good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"understanding of BSW configuration of each module","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"new","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"new","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes its really good and got basic knowledge on AUTOSAR BSW configuration. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7241bfd8e99600170e7fcf"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567769022993"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567769022993"},"name":"Karthikeyan Sundaram","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti Osram","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Sivaram covered all question with respect to project question, very excellent. more than expectation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"RTE and CoM stack integration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"SecOc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"12 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"DAI projects","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":"nice"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"May be PPT for advanced training and Time is not sufficient to cover advanced training like this training","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d725735f9226500179b46af"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1567774517845"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1567774517845"},"name":"Punith B","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti Osram","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberDouble":"3.5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberDouble":"4.5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Practical approach"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"all","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"drivers","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"rte, diagnostics","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, :D","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d75d858c97c570017564668"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568004184193"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568004184193"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-05 to 2019-09-06","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I came to know all the information about EB "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Got a chance to interact with all teams","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NIL","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, It can be some interactive fun activities.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d79fe2cbed05d001718ae75"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568276012985"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568276012985"},"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","training":"Train the trainer","trainers":"Anand","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The trainer was precise in the content that he planned to deliver and executed perfectly"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The contents","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"The nuances with which the trainer have delivered his content itself was a learning and the constant linking of the concepts to his handling of the training was the best part.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7a3f87f162120017ee9101"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568292743573"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568292743573"},"name":"SANJAYA KUMAR PANDA","training":"Train the trainer","trainers":"Anand","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"DIFFERENT ROLES TO  PLAY IN A TRAINING"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"1. ADMINISTRATOR FACILITATOR 3. INSTRUCTOR ROLE DURING TRAINING ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"REAL TIME DEMO ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 YEAR","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"EB CORBOS STUDIO","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"1. ADMINISTRATOR FACILITATOR 3. INSTRUCTOR ROLE DURING TRAINING ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b27db04e5b100170980ca"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568352219023"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568352219023"},"name":"Syed Abrar Hussaini","training":"Train the trainer","trainers":"Anand","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Yes, I am excited to apply this in my career as a trainer."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Recording the video and self assessment.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I don't think anything was missed","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Application development.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. I have a lot of new things that I can adapt in the upcoming training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b2b8a04e5b100170980cb"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568353162875"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568353162875"},"name":"","training":"Train the trainer","trainers":"Anand","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anand","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"How prepare the long / short session plan, to make impact on audience."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Structure of the Training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"everything was covered.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For my upcoming Training plans ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes I am satisfied with the training. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b4cc014bde20017aacb45"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568361664508"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568361664508"},"name":"Nanditha","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Detailed explanation and examples with hands on"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on training on the relevant topics","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 week","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Unit test","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b4cf514bde20017aacb46"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568361717353"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568361717353"},"name":"","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b4d6b14bde20017aacb47"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568361835753"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568361835753"},"name":"Abhinav Singh","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"BDD practical session","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b4d6c14bde20017aacb48"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568361836773"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568361836773"},"name":"","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"More programming than theory. So the session went very useful."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Programming","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"some respective domain examples would have helped","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Testing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, I have completely satisfied. But  some people are talkative too much . no manners on how to behave in meetings. kindly educate such people.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b4d8314bde20017aacb49"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568361859120"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568361859120"},"name":"","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Understood about the BDD Concept"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands-on training was given effectively","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Most of the topics were covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Currently not using any EB product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes .well satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b4fb914bde20017aacb4a"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568362425573"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568362425573"},"name":"Shabari Eshwarprasad","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"More practical in approach and clarity of the subject helped us in getting clarity","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"One of the good feature of ma'am was that she listened carefully to our queries and answered practically","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"Very well versed","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"Ma'am made sure that the session is interactive and that everybody's involvement was present","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"We clarified our queries w.r.t. the expectations of the client for the project that I work on and we got relevant clarification. We might need to implement these ideas in our current project"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Ma'am listened to our queries patiently and answered with relevant demo, which helped us in understanding the subject well","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Not that I am aware of","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For development of the stories and to achieve in-sprint automation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. This training helped us with the way forward in our current project, which could bring in value to the client. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b6854ea717100179cb41e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568368724591"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568368724591"},"name":"Ipsita Das","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The content was good and it was very informative but one thing, it would have been better if we knew what tools and jar files could be installed prior to the session"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Way of teaching","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 week","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Testing and training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b6855ea717100179cb41f"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568368725377"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568368725377"},"name":"Ipsita Das","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The content was good and it was very informative but one thing, it would have been better if we knew what tools and jar files could be installed prior to the session"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Way of teaching","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 week","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Testing and training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b6855ea717100179cb420"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568368725387"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568368725387"},"name":"Ipsita Das","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The content was good and it was very informative but one thing, it would have been better if we knew what tools and jar files could be installed prior to the session"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Way of teaching","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 week","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Testing and training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7b6856ea717100179cb421"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568368726005"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568368726005"},"name":"Ipsita Das","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The content was good and it was very informative but one thing, it would have been better if we knew what tools and jar files could be installed prior to the session"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Way of teaching","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 week","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Testing and training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7efc73eb53470017bb8a81"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568603251890"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568603251890"},"name":"sangeeta","training":"BDD","trainers":"Nirmala","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12 to 2019-09-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"},"comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Nirmala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Helpful for unit testing, "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"conversion of customer requirement into system requirements.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"guidance for installing and setup the software.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 week","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"unit test","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Knowledge of the testing for developer is helpful, so that product becomes stable. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d7f108e869f210017c6b4a0"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1568608398866"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1568608398866"},"name":"Lokesh Uppara","training":"Train the trainer","trainers":"Philip David","location":"EB India","date":"2019-09-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Philip David","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Philip David","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Philip David","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Philip David","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Feedback on presentation excises is good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2+","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Technical training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, satisfied.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d8b44f46514ae0017c0c10c"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408244060"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408244060"},"name":"A","training":"EB Tresos Studio Training","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Aswathy Vijayan","location":"Continental","date":"2019-09-24 to 2019-09-25","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Hands-on session"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM module configuration ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NO IDEA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NO Previous experience ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"New project requirement ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good training for beginners ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d8b44f46514ae0017c0c10d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408244197"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408244197"},"name":"A","training":"EB Tresos Studio Training","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Aswathy Vijayan","location":"Continental","date":"2019-09-24 to 2019-09-25","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Hands-on session"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM module configuration ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NO IDEA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NO Previous experience ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"New project requirement ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good training for beginners ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d8b45636514ae0017c0c10e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408355670"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408355670"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Studio Training","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Aswathy Vijayan","location":"Continental","date":"2019-09-24 to 2019-09-25","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"Quality of content is good."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":"Good"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"If you have autosar knowledge "},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Examples"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Practical sessions ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Better do training with basic Autosar module ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d8b457a6514ae0017c0c10f"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408378733"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408378733"},"name":"Someswara Rao Badana","training":"EB Tresos Studio Training","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Aswathy Vijayan","location":"Continental","date":"2019-09-24 to 2019-09-25","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"no"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"comstak and memstack hands on","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"if it will be mode handson...it could be better","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"all BSW","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"i am satisfied, if person doesn't know about Eb tools, this training is very much use full to start.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d8b469d6514ae0017c0c110"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408669944"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408669944"},"name":"Rajesh Nagarajan","training":"EB Tresos Studio Training","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Aswathy Vijayan","location":"Continental","date":"2019-09-24 to 2019-09-25","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"EB tresos tools"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on experience with presentations","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"DCM","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"DCM","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Pls make introduce in Autosar general to refresh people to recall their understanding","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d8b46e36514ae0017c0c111"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408739271"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408739271"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Studio Training","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Aswathy Vijayan","location":"Continental","date":"2019-09-24 to 2019-09-25","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":" "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"practical session","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"adding cdd module, good explanation for 1st day topics","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW module configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes. got good overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d8b46fe6514ae0017c0c112"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408766756"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1569408766756"},"name":"Karthik G","training":"EB Tresos Studio Training","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Aswathy Vijayan","location":"Continental","date":"2019-09-24 to 2019-09-25","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"5\n3","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"5\n3","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"5\n3","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"5\n4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Most of the training exercise had already implemented sections ( Implementation from user was little). Trainer was good but scope of training was less."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands-on exercise","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Module exercise and theory session session for it should have been more.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"DCM, DEM","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"YES","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d8b4dc06514ae0017c0c113"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1569410496613"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1569410496613"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Studio Training","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Aswathy Vijayan","location":"Continental","date":"2019-09-24 to 2019-09-25","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Hands on excersise was good which was covering the a view to configure and understand the flow"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Able to understand the basics of configuring","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d8cb8ac0e3dfa001789c409"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1569503404331"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1569503404331"},"name":"Raghavendra Kariyannavar","training":"EB Tresos Studio Training","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Aswathy Vijayan","location":"Continental","date":"2019-09-24 to 2019-09-25","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aswathy Vijayan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"adding module and configuring"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuration of module and interaction between other modules","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"module development demo","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Never used","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"not now, but use in future","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, I enjoyed the training, but may include some more practical/hands on topics in the first day itself.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d9f14329abe0e0017f0d07b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1570706482629"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1570706482629"},"name":"Raja G","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"He can give some more examples i feel."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I waited since our last \"German inter cultural workshop\" program. Now i am part of it :)","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"knife, fork, and spoon i think.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"no idea","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"no idea","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Thanks all for arranging this workshop.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d9f21905df78e00177f82b9"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1570709904191"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1570709904191"},"name":"Jaladhi Vyas","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Exercises"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Examples","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Not missed","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. It's very informative and interesting. Trainer is very energetic","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d9fec1ca00f4f0017216f58"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1570761756486"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1570761756486"},"name":"Kavyashree B.E","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The way trainer was interacting with people,its was more of 2 way communication."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"How to be assertive and yet softspoken.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"May be the dining etiqutte","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"10months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"May be while interaction with out counter parts","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yea, I am very much satisfied with the training. Looking forward for more such trainings.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d9fed51a00f4f0017216f59"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1570762065321"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1570762065321"},"name":"","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Contents of the training"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Asertive thinking","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2+ months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Implementation w.r.t client relation ship build, product delivery, work life balance","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d9fefc8a00f4f0017216f5a"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1570762696436"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1570762696436"},"name":"Mohan Krishna B","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"More in-depth culture of Germany required"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"flexibility to adapt to people","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"actual daily behavior in germany","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"14 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"daily meetings","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da04b5b056f2d0017dc9dc5"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1570786139068"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1570786139068"},"name":"Pankaj Pande","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"More instances contents on German Culture would have been good."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"Contents shall be specific to German culture other country culture shall be avoided to avoid confusion."}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"Collective interaction is required, I noticed that few participants were feeling bored.","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the exercises, but felt more specific exercises and country information should have been provided."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Respecting Time and Space","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Dinning etiquettes, though participants discussed on it, but this should have been part of cource agned/contents.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"10 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"AUTOSAR ECU Extract Import","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, I am satisfied with the training. But still feel, there are some other common things to learn about German culture.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da05b4b53a20200171b3d82"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1570790219162"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1570790219162"},"name":"Nikitha Mandhana","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Assertive Behaviour"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Assertive Behaviour","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"May be more examples of how germans differ in their culture.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes I am satisfied with the training ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da4078d58cb610017fed49f"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571030925453"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571030925453"},"name":"Manushree T S","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Assertive communication"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Assertive communication","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Not sure","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"There was a problem with speakers which was not sorted for a long time"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Informative and Interactive","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da447ed70ff1f00179b8027"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571047405149"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571047405149"},"name":"Shreedhar","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"How to say no.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"About food, festival, living culture.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 Year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Daily activity ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training was good, but would have covered some more topics about German culture like their food, festival and etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da4489c70ff1f00179b8028"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571047580886"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571047580886"},"name":"Manidhar Mulaparthi ","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Saying No in pleasent way."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Say No. Wait analyze & understand others culture or state before reacting.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Not sure.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"5months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Car infotainment","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da44e8870ff1f00179b8029"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571049096220"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571049096220"},"name":"","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The real time examples with exercises."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I heard there use to be a lunch etiquette session which was missing. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"10 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"satisfactory.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da4523b70ff1f00179b802a"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571050043948"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571050043948"},"name":"Chandan","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the way he approached with culture differences, As an improvement i think he has to speak more about german culture"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercises","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"German food culture, weather, and more details on germany","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1.5 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Testing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Would like to know more about german culture rather than general","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da458b670ff1f00179b802b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571051702270"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571051702270"},"name":"Shubhi Agarwal","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The trainning is more interactive "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The german culture is the most valuable part of the training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I don't think so any topic is left out ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Few months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Be strict to the point","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, I am satisfied with the training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da545ca5dfd03001766adb4"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571112394658"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571112394658"},"name":"Thilepan","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"They how james explained the cultural difference between place and people"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Behavioral difference between cultures","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"no idea about the missing this as i am new to these types of programs","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Acceptance testing and SW testing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes, i am satisfied with this training","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da6d15d3ab75b001771197e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571213661861"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571213661861"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy,Sachin Shivakumar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-09 to 2019-10-11","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Explanation with real time example"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No idea","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2.5 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Tool developer","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"3 days are not enough for this kind of training, need to bit extend the time of training like 3.5 or 4 days for more clarity and question for doubts.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da6e2bfe4a8ea00175dcb49"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571218111736"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571218111736"},"name":"Madhavi","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"case studies covered"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3.5 yrs","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da6ee96e4a8ea00175dcb4d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571221142148"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571221142148"},"name":"Surjashis Mukherjee","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"excellent","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"excellent","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"superb","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"very nice","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"No, as we were expecting hands-on with EB tresos to configure & evaluate EB stack which we would purchase."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"CAN stack configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Ethernet stack details","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Will use ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"This is an awareness training and introduction to EB Tresos tool. We expected a little bit more in terms of actual EB stack usage and configurations.  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da704c3967dc50017d73ea5"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571226819232"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571226819232"},"name":"Dhananjay Bangar","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Autosar concepts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"SWC","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"no first time i have work with EB","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"RET code generation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da704ed967dc50017d73ea6"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571226861074"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571226861074"},"name":"Dattatraya Bora","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation contents"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"EB tresos configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercise, Training evaluation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"EB tresos classic Autosar beginner","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Classic AUTOSAR configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training contents are good. Need to improve on Time for training practices and Online evaluation after training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da705ed967dc50017d73ea7"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227117981"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227117981"},"name":"bhupesh patil","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"\n","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"\n","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"\n","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"\n","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Diag stack."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"OS configration and Com stack excersie ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"DoIp in diag","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Configration of BSW","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes,\nIn CAN module you guys need to add reception of messages as well.\ngive some assessment test after training.\n","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da70631967dc50017d73ea8"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227185106"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227185106"},"name":"Sayali Salape","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Configuration part parallel with concepts."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Tool configuration for different modules","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No longer","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"AUTOSAR stack configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. If possible provide more detailed configurations for different modules like ethernet, multi-core configuration etc.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da70670967dc50017d73ea9"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227248891"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227248891"},"name":"Manjushree Patil","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Get familiar with Autosar concepts and tool"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Practical session & excersises on tool ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Safety,Security","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"New to EB product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For our POC","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.\nI would like to request you for the assessment of this tanning.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da7073a967dc50017d73eaa"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227450559"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227450559"},"name":"Pratiksha Ghule","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Overall knowledge of Autosar and Tool"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"ComStack , Swc, RTC configuration ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Ethernet communication configuration in EB tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3days","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For configuring the BSW SWC, RTE and MCAL","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, I learned how to configure the SWC, RTE, BSW using EB tool.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da707bb967dc50017d73eab"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227579942"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227579942"},"name":"Mohan Rao","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"More detailed exercise with real problem statement would have helped"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Actual field side example","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"4 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Proof of concept to start witj","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"it was good as beginner to understand the basics of Elektrobit stack and tools","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da7082f967dc50017d73eac"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227695015"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227695015"},"name":"Deepti Mahajan","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"Properly structured. \nSuggestion is to add steps / sequence diagram for modules that will help in better understanding while configuring the tool."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":"Good "},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.50","comments":"Knowledgable","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"Few topics were covered too fast. ","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Being new to Autosar domain, faced challenge in relating tool configuration to terminology, content, configuration from specifications. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Autosar concepts and basic tool understanding. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"CAN - Full and basic can, Memory module details, Watchdog manager, I/O drivers in detail,State machines of different modules","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"New to Autosar and EB product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"POC ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Overall training was good and informative. Material was structured properly covering basics of each layer in Autosar and respective modules.\n\nSuggestion: It will be helpful if training content is delivered in slow pace considering participants are new to domain and tool in order to relate better.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da7087d967dc50017d73ead"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227773280"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571227773280"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Communication Stack, SWC & RTE generation with Tresos."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Com stack hands on example","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Ethernet Stack explanation with example.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"New to EB product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"AUTOSAR BSW stack configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"It would be helpful if training evaluation questions can be provided"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training is in line with EB Tresos tool usage. Could be better if more hands on example are provided in training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da70b45967dc50017d73eae"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571228485244"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571228485244"},"name":"Amrut Kulkarni","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Topics covered were good "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuring the SWC, BSW Components, Communication Stack in tresos tool was more value.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Ethernet/IP stack was missed. Can include some more practical exercise as  well as Autosar concept are vast","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No previous work experience on EB tools and product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":"For Creating the Autosar awareness this is good training.  "},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Can have more hands on Tools and it have huge configuration parameters.\nCan include training evaluation to check the understand-ability   ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da70c8c967dc50017d73eaf"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571228812850"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571228812850"},"name":"Supriya Chavan","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Einfochips - Pune ","date":"2019-10-14 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Got autosar concepts and configurations done with EB tool."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Practical Examples, HandsOn Examples","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Advanced concept","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Configurations of BSW,SWC,RTE.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da7da12f5661c0017583bc2"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571281426659"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571281426659"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy,Sachin Shivakumar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-09 to 2019-10-11","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the overall structure of the training and the way it was presented and the relevance of the hands-on"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Understanding the basics and hands-on","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Highly satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da811faaba1be00175becf6"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571295738335"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571295738335"},"name":"Biswajit Jana","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da81776aba1be00175becf7"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571297142156"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571297142156"},"name":"Besly Thomas K","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"Excellent Presentation"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":"Learned more about the attitude and values of Germans."},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"Very practical and interesting"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":"Well planned"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"Nice presentation","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Interactive sessions"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"understanding the values of German culture","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NIL","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Software","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da832dd4b9b5b00173082e9"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571304157670"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571304157670"},"name":"saurabh vishwakarma","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"how to talk with german people"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"How to say \"No\"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No one ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"time punctuality","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da838964b9b5b00173082ea"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571305622688"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571305622688"},"name":"","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"How to be Assertive!"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Being assertive and knowing german culture","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More content on German culture","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"AAV","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. It was little more of Indian culture content.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da83a594b9b5b00173082eb"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571306073622"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571306073622"},"name":"","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-10","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Its to learn about German values and their working style"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"What things needed to taken care while writing a mail to a German colleague/customer","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I thinks more activities need to be included in the syllabus","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"I have worked with EB Guide with 2-3 months ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"It was for a project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, It was good .","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5da989c8d59d73001719437e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571391944531"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571391944531"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy,Sachin Shivakumar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-09 to 2019-10-11","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Excercises"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"RTE & OS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"OS Excercises","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"8","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Integration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daac2bcafe1cf001739c4b2"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571472060721"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571472060721"},"name":"Shripad Joshi","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"More hands on examples in appreciated"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"AUTOSAR related information and tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Lots of practice, of course more time is needed","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, would love to make some hands on experience by own. Post support is expected","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daad633afe1cf001739c4b3"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477043069"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477043069"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Content covered in Training"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Safety, IO abstraction layer, CDD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Have wored on Mentor graphics tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"MCAL and BSW","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daad67cafe1cf001739c4b4"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477116751"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477116751"},"name":"Milind Thorat","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"More practical examples for configuration of BSW modules "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"configuration of BSW modules ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daad68dafe1cf001739c4b5"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477133902"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477133902"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Diagnostic part was covered more theoritically no hands on"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"CANstack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More hands -on ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"7 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"More hands on and good documentation will improve the quality ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daad75eafe1cf001739c4b6"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477342964"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477342964"},"name":"SUTAR ABHIJIT D","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"All the contents were up to the expectation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands-on Exercise","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Need to add more exercises which can be practiced after training completion. Also it would be good, if we can have video tutorials.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For ADAS ECU development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It is very good training to start with Autosar. Also feeling happy as EB has provided 2-3 months eval copy so that we can practice what we learned in training. Will definitely recommend this training to others as well. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daad846afe1cf001739c4b7"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477574798"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477574798"},"name":"Gaurav Kedari","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked hand-on part."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All training was valuable for me.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Ethernet stack and Functional safety.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"8 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuration and generation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daad8beafe1cf001739c4b8"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477694932"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477694932"},"name":"SUPRIYA MHATRE","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"Good and highly detailed content"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Training Material "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW Configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercise on Ethernet communication","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Integration and Application SWC development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":"Applicable mostly in BSW configuration"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":"Overall good training and explaination"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Thank you!!","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daad8dfafe1cf001739c4b9"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477727088"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571477727088"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"the stacks covered are explanatory enough.Can include more service elements."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"AUTOSAR Basic theoratical concepts & Hands-on of the tresos tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"practical demo on Diagnostics,top to bottom SWC integration ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Haven't used","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW configuration,MCAL integration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training was good. Good explanation of concepts. But Hands-On part should be more. We would definitely recommend others for this training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daadf6aafe1cf001739c4ba"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571479402856"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571479402856"},"name":"GB","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"COM stack heory and configuration"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"EB Tool Hands on","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Advanced concepts of SWCs (Interrunnable Variables, Exclusive areas)","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Never used yet","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Will use for BSW configuration and code generation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daae735afe1cf001739c4bb"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571481397388"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571481397388"},"name":"Shailesh P. Kharche","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Training approach"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Handson","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Security","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"New for EB","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes....nice training contents","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daae82cafe1cf001739c4bc"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571481644848"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571481644848"},"name":"Dnyaneshwar Kashid ","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Kunvar Abhishek Jain","location":"Magna - Pune","date":"2019-10-17 to 2019-10-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"\n","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.50","comments":"\n","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"\n","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"\n","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Autosar concepts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"EB tresos use","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Security ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW , RTE &  SWC configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daff1bc45d2c1001701c89d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571811772262"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571811772262"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"2","comments":"RTE is a huge topic. It is difficult to cover in 2 days in detail."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"More examples like using different interfaces & service SWC etc would be helpful"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Examples for each topic wasnt clearly understood/explained"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Other types of interface like mode switch interface with example","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Stack integration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Not completely. As i mentioned, RTE topic training is difficult to complete in 2 days including demo. Exercises like pseudo coding and concentrating on EB tool usage wasnt necessary. Instead could have covered other RTE topics in detail.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5daff5ce45d2c1001701c89e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571812814274"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571812814274"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"All generic cases are explained"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"Could have explained with more practical configuration examples"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"Confused with terms like task functions/runnables","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"1.00","comments":"Created lot of confusion","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"1"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"1"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Should have been advanced training as all participants already have basic knowledge on RTE and works on tresos daily basis"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"There are a lot of topics missing, mainly interaction of RTE & OS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Development & integration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":"Agenda to be cleared first"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"No. Trainers were not able to answer queries on use cases other than very generic ones. Trainers tried their best but it seems like they dont have much of practical experience and explained everything theoretically. Not really satisfied with content could have been better.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db005ecac53cc0017763da6"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571816940409"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571816940409"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"2","comments":"Content was not explained in detail"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"Should have focused on RTE topics more."},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"1st day morning session was for beginners of Autosar. 2nd day, usage of EB tool demo was not required."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"2.00","comments":"The flow was not maintained","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"Could have explained in a more better way","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"No much examples were given","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"It is ok","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"EB tool usage & RTE introduction with writing a code could have been skipped because the agenda was already shared. RTE topic in detail was expected. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NVM service SWC, code generation examples with API, mode switch interface","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"EB tresos from 2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For BSW layer","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":"Content was explained poorly"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":"Time was not sufficient. Things were rusted"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":"Still few things are not clear"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":"trainers need to have indepth knowledge"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training should be of 3 days. EB tool demo & code writing example is already covered in Autosar training, so it was not required. We wanted more knowledge on RTE. The trainers seems to have not much knowledge in depth. The concepts were not explained in detail and clear.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db005edac53cc0017763da7"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571816941299"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571816941299"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"2","comments":"Content was not explained in detail"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"Should have focused on RTE topics more."},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"1st day morning session was for beginners of Autosar. 2nd day, usage of EB tool demo was not required."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"2.00","comments":"The flow was not maintained","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"Could have explained in a more better way","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"No much examples were given","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"It is ok","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"EB tool usage & RTE introduction with writing a code could have been skipped because the agenda was already shared. RTE topic in detail was expected. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NVM service SWC, code generation examples with API, mode switch interface","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"EB tresos from 2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For BSW layer","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":"Content was explained poorly"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":"Time was not sufficient. Things were rusted"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":"Still few things are not clear"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":"trainers need to have indepth knowledge"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training should be of 3 days. EB tool demo & code writing example is already covered in Autosar training, so it was not required. We wanted more knowledge on RTE. The trainers seems to have not much knowledge in depth. The concepts were not explained in detail and clear.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db00760ac53cc0017763da8"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571817312737"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571817312737"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"The content of PPT presented during the session was good"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"It would have been explained with example."},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"Presentation was good","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"trainers were not aware of certain concepts what we were expecting","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Whatever was presented we were already knowing, expected some deep level training and not the basic concepts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Demo","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1.5 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Integration & configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"We expected the training as per the agenda we provided with respect to the problem we face. It didnt meet our expectations. Training didnt happen as per the agenda provided.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db00821ac53cc0017763da9"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571817505191"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571817505191"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Trainers were not experts on the topic and since the participants were not beginners it was difficult for the trainers."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"RTE - OS - BSWM interface","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Module configurations and OS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"No.We expected experts to take the training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db009bdac53cc0017763daa"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571817917375"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571817917375"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"The first exercise was not really adding value as all participants were aware of Autosar."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":"Expectation was to have more detailed & step by step explaination"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"It would have beeen better if creating one service SWC & App in SWC from scratch."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"Expecting to have follow diagram to understand logical structure and what is the difference between 2 different interface, 2 different events."}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Expected to understand all service layer SWC"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Theory explaination","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Indepth explaination","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Timing, OI","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Expectation was to have complete system level knowledge, OS, service needs. Only RTE is not enough when there is dependency.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db00a2dac53cc0017763dab"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571818029747"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571818029747"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":" "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db00ae2ac53cc0017763dac"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571818210626"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571818210626"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"Content was good but some topics were missed as requested earlier"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"1","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Understandability would have been improved"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Interactions RTE with OS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"SW platform","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Not reached our expectations","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db00be2ac53cc0017763dad"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571818466406"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571818466406"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"EB experts with advance knowledge in topics need to take the training. People who have worked with EB products for more years than the attendees."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"basics was fine","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"In depth questions were not answered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1+ year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW module configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"1","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"No, I am not satisfied.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db00c60ac53cc0017763dae"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571818592776"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571818592776"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":" "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Starting activity","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Flow of the contents is missing because of more doubts from participants","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Platform","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db00fb2ac53cc0017763daf"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571819442141"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571819442141"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"2","comments":"Demo shall be adopted to RTE training. RTE concepts and visual flows of config created"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"Same as explained above"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"For me RTE training should have been tailored for RTE specific training. However, content from EB Autosar training is re-used again. I suggest you to have following flow for next training. 1) RTE concepts - Basic. 2) What tools used for RTE. 3) Visual flow of config of SWC - RTE - BSW. 4) Can plan separate session for RTE basic and advanced. 5) Use case RTE-NVM; RTE-CoM; RTE- DEM/DET with simple demo, flow can be explained"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW Integration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Same points from 3. Training shall be tailored/customised for RTE. It shall not be subset of normal EB Autosar training. Otherwise people will have same content who attended these 2 trainings","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db01041ac53cc0017763db0"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571819585894"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571819585894"},"name":"","training":"RTE","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"Continental","date":"2019-10-15 to 2019-10-16","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"2","comments":"demo is not useful. It will be useful only for beginner"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"Can be added more exercise"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"trainers are also developers, not experts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"No.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db13c5f2947cf0017b92bb6"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571896415070"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571896415070"},"name":"Naresh","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Products & Projects."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The Mission & Vission of EB.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"< 1 month.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"EB Corbos for HPC Development tasks.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Very Good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db13dc02947cf0017b92bb7"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571896768849"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571896768849"},"name":"Varun S","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"HR , Product Overview"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"ALL ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 month ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"MCAL configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db147d247cf4a00177d2929"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571899346177"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571899346177"},"name":"Ashish Hariharan","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"The Corporate overview could be made Primary in the list. Then the Subsequesnt divisions like Project innovations and Product"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Covered the required fields necessary for a new joinee. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Corporte overview, HR, Information Security","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Sessions of Global travel management would be preferrable","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Classic AUTOSAR configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"I am satisfied with the training, But the Agenda and sessions list were shared just before the starting time, it could be shared bit earlier.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db1487647cf4a00177d292a"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571899510042"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571899510042"},"name":"shilparani","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Products Overview is the one which I liked the most"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All sessions were important","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All topics are covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes satisfied ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db14cf447cf4a00177d292b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571900660511"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571900660511"},"name":"Ghanshyam","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"All queries were answered well and all the trainers are perfect in their respective role."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Products, Projects & HR","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Introduction with Managing Director was missing. Good to have for 5-10 mins interaction with EB India Head (If he is free) ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not yet worked","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes! satisfied with the training.\nOne suggestion. Access and ID cards should be given within 2-3 days to new joiner.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db151ff47cf4a00177d292c"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571901951711"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571901951711"},"name":"sangeeta","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"information is really helpful for employees"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"IT security","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It will be useful for employee . thank you","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db1525f47cf4a00177d292d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571902047160"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571902047160"},"name":"Ravi Rathod","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"All the session was so interactive and helpful "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Project over view, HR and IT security","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"corporate overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db16179af2f5f0017b16622"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571905913313"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571905913313"},"name":"Simma Geetha","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The interactive explanation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"About the company","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yeah I satisfied. Its good to know about organization","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db27eb8e9c76000174ea847"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936459"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936459"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"3","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"In General the topics of Induction shall be revisited.  The Topic shall also include some of the common Tools or services used in EB eg.Jeera,SVN,Cruise control, Jenkins.  Though team people would help us and there are videos which would help, it would be great if these topoics are explained by the experts of those particular Tool/service. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"common technical topics like Jeera, SVN, CC, Jenkins. etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db27eb8e9c76000174ea848"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936656"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936656"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"3","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"In General the topics of Induction shall be revisited.  The Topic shall also include some of the common Tools or services used in EB eg.Jeera,SVN,Cruise control, Jenkins.  Though team people would help us and there are videos which would help, it would be great if these topoics are explained by the experts of those particular Tool/service. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"common technical topics like Jeera, SVN, CC, Jenkins. etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db27eb8e9c76000174ea849"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936717"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936717"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"3","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"In General the topics of Induction shall be revisited.  The Topic shall also include some of the common Tools or services used in EB eg.Jeera,SVN,Cruise control, Jenkins.  Though team people would help us and there are videos which would help, it would be great if these topoics are explained by the experts of those particular Tool/service. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"common technical topics like Jeera, SVN, CC, Jenkins. etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db27eb8e9c76000174ea84a"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936721"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936721"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"3","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"In General the topics of Induction shall be revisited.  The Topic shall also include some of the common Tools or services used in EB eg.Jeera,SVN,Cruise control, Jenkins.  Though team people would help us and there are videos which would help, it would be great if these topoics are explained by the experts of those particular Tool/service. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"common technical topics like Jeera, SVN, CC, Jenkins. etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db27eb8e9c76000174ea84b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936852"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936852"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"3","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"In General the topics of Induction shall be revisited.  The Topic shall also include some of the common Tools or services used in EB eg.Jeera,SVN,Cruise control, Jenkins.  Though team people would help us and there are videos which would help, it would be great if these topoics are explained by the experts of those particular Tool/service. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"common technical topics like Jeera, SVN, CC, Jenkins. etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db27eb8e9c76000174ea84c"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936880"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936880"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"3","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"In General the topics of Induction shall be revisited.  The Topic shall also include some of the common Tools or services used in EB eg.Jeera,SVN,Cruise control, Jenkins.  Though team people would help us and there are videos which would help, it would be great if these topoics are explained by the experts of those particular Tool/service. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"common technical topics like Jeera, SVN, CC, Jenkins. etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db27eb8e9c76000174ea84d"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936962"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978936962"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"3","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"In General the topics of Induction shall be revisited.  The Topic shall also include some of the common Tools or services used in EB eg.Jeera,SVN,Cruise control, Jenkins.  Though team people would help us and there are videos which would help, it would be great if these topoics are explained by the experts of those particular Tool/service. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"common technical topics like Jeera, SVN, CC, Jenkins. etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db27eb9e9c76000174ea84e"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978937071"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978937071"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"3","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"In General the topics of Induction shall be revisited.  The Topic shall also include some of the common Tools or services used in EB eg.Jeera,SVN,Cruise control, Jenkins.  Though team people would help us and there are videos which would help, it would be great if these topoics are explained by the experts of those particular Tool/service. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"common technical topics like Jeera, SVN, CC, Jenkins. etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db27eb9e9c76000174ea84f"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978937343"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571978937343"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-23 to 2019-10-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"3","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"In General the topics of Induction shall be revisited.  The Topic shall also include some of the common Tools or services used in EB eg.Jeera,SVN,Cruise control, Jenkins.  Though team people would help us and there are videos which would help, it would be great if these topoics are explained by the experts of those particular Tool/service. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"common technical topics like Jeera, SVN, CC, Jenkins. etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db28f6ebec18f0017a51d52"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571983214315"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571983214315"},"name":"Ajay Rawat","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy,Sachin Shivakumar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-09 to 2019-10-11","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"Quality of content was good."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":"In the integration it will play a vital role,to execute the work flow and what to do if new components are added and new connections are made."},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":"It was important for my work perspective."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the examples they gave regarding the topics."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on and the concepts explaination part","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Everything was covered.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3-4 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Adding the preconfig rules.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes I am satisfied with training .One additional improvement that can be done is in the slides part.Some concepts can be presented with the examples so that it can be easy to visualise.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db290e3bec18f0017a51d53"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571983587723"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571983587723"},"name":"Rohit Raj","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy,Sachin Shivakumar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-09 to 2019-10-11","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"1"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Good overview of Autosar and EB Tresos tool"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"overview of Autosar and EB Tresos tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Due to short duration most of the modules were taken up fastly","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Requirement implementation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db294a7bec18f0017a51d54"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571984551691"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571984551691"},"name":"Sivakumar A","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy,Sachin Shivakumar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-09 to 2019-10-11","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"quality of content is very good, "},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The 3-Layered AUTOSAR Architecture"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The 3-Layered AUTOSAR Architecture, EB TRESOS STUDIO","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No topics were missed, covered all the topics ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 YEARS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"TRESOS STUDIO DEVELOPMENT","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Over all training went of well , it was valuable.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5db2add03c29a900175f685b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1571990992711"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1571990992711"},"name":"Kuldip Balgonda Miraje","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy,Sachin Shivakumar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-10-09 to 2019-10-11","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Pavithra Kumaraswamy","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sachin Shivakumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"How communication works in AUTOSAR Modules"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"RTE ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Need to explain more on Operating Systems.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"8 Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Integration ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, with this training we are able to understand Classic AUTOSAR workflow, the importance of RTE, and hands-on training on communication between the Different Modules.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dce5978a818170017f4c689"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental Singapore","date":"2019-11-13 to 2019-11-15","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"able to clarify previous doubts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"q & a, exercises","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"data implementation types, compu methods, detailed info on ports","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1.5 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"assembly connectors, rte editing, os editing, generating templates","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1573804408044"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1573804408044"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dce5a39a818170017f4c68a"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental Singapore","date":"2019-11-13 to 2019-11-15","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"BSW modules were hard for people without autosar experience.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"need more hours for BSW modules"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Idea regarding entire system","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"ASW configuration ,Diagnostiocs configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Project sytem code generation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1573804601610"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1573804601610"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dce5a41a818170017f4c68b"},"name":"LEE WILSON","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental Singapore","date":"2019-11-13 to 2019-11-15","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Hand-on exercise giving by the training which make the session more meaningful and understandable"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hand-on exercise","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yup. I am satisfied with the training. The training give us a guideline where should begin with as well as the software architecture and concept.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1573804609689"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1573804609689"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dce5c3da818170017f4c68c"},"name":"Liu Chaoyi","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental Singapore","date":"2019-11-13 to 2019-11-15","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":"As I do not have any background of AUTOSAR, this training is very helpful in giving an overview of the AUTOSAR system."},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"Due to time constraint, we need to go through the exercise quickly. It could be better that the slides can contain some mappings from the theory (flow of configuration) to the relevant Tresos windows."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":"Very clear structure."}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"Concise and Coherent presentation.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"The trainer is able to give impromptu response to the audience's questions. The answers given are clear.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I like the overall structure of the training which first covered theory part and then demonstrates how theory can be mapped into practice through the hands on exercises."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I appreciate the hands-on training the most.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"As an introductory training, the coverage is comprehensive. Due to time constraint, we need to go through the exercise quickly. It could be better that the slides can contain some mappings from the theory (flow of configuration) to the relevant Tresos windows.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"I have not started using EB product yet.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":"It is most beneficial to those who have no prior experience with AUTOSAR but with some knowledge of OSEK."},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"This training gives an excellent introduction to the overall structure of AUTOSAR framework and how EB's tresos product realizes the AUTOSAR framework. The hands-on exercises re-enforces the understanding of the theory and gives quick feedback to the audience on how well they understands the topics covered in the training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1573805117146"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1573805117146"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dce61a4a818170017f4c68d"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental Singapore","date":"2019-11-13 to 2019-11-15","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1573806500148"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1573806500148"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dce6786a818170017f4c68e"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental Singapore","date":"2019-11-13 to 2019-11-15","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Enough explanation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"AUTOSAR workflow","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1573808006256"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1573808006256"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dce6813a818170017f4c68f"},"name":"Ooi Xi Sheng","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental Singapore","date":"2019-11-13 to 2019-11-15","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Config of CAN stack with explaination"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"CAN configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All generic topics were touched","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For work","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1573808147311"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1573808147311"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dce6aafa818170017f4c690"},"name":"Lee Men Hwa","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Continental Singapore","date":"2019-11-13 to 2019-11-15","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I like the hand-on parts, it gives me better overview and understanding."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Understanding of the overall (basic) usage of the Tresos tool.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Basically it covered all the ACG modules, unless there is other scope out of ACG, else nothing is missing.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For automotive controller software development.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, the training is well organized.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1573808815671"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1573808815671"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd7d937da9b560017df26a3"},"name":"BJ Rajendranath","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Saran Kumar","location":"TVS Motor- Bangalore","date":"2019-11-20 to 2019-11-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"RTE"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"RTE","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"SWC","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Application Development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574426935892"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574426935892"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd7dfdfda9b560017df26a4"},"name":"Mansoor Basheer","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Saran Kumar","location":"TVS Motor- Bangalore","date":"2019-11-20 to 2019-11-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"Well documented and structured."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":"Good."},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":"Exercise gave excellent walk through to basics of Autosar."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":"Very well structured."}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"Excellent. ","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"Excellent.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"Knowledge level is really good.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"Excellent. Clarified all doubts and questions.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Way of teaching."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercise work","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Not much.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574428639263"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574428639263"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddb43030a9ff100170892de"},"name":"Harigovindh","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Saran Kumar","location":"TVS Motor- Bangalore","date":"2019-11-20 to 2019-11-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Hands on session"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on section","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"System architecture design- autosar authoring tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Embedded coding","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good learning","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574650627438"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574650627438"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddb45420a9ff100170892df"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Saran Kumar","location":"TVS Motor- Bangalore","date":"2019-11-20 to 2019-11-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"Response time of Akhil was quite less.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"All the questions and doubts has been answered and cleared by the presenters."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The session on RTE and Application layer are valuable.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Almost all the topics are covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"I havent worked with the EB product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For our upcoming projects ,to make our SW common for any controllers","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes I am satisfied with the training sessions.The session was very interactive and the energy level of the presenters remained same till the end .The  presenters welcomed our doubts and cleared without any negligence.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574651202563"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574651202563"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddb47320a9ff100170892e0"},"name":"SHIVAM DHARMENDRASINH CHUDASAMA","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Saran Kumar","location":"TVS Motor- Bangalore","date":"2019-11-20 to 2019-11-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"basic concept of AUTOSAR made clear"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"software handson","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"more practise on software","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574651698769"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574651698769"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddb49ef0a9ff100170892e1"},"name":"ARJUN RAVEENDRANATH","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Saran Kumar","location":"TVS Motor- Bangalore","date":"2019-11-20 to 2019-11-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"Exercises were good, but because they were planned in short spells, entire workflow was not very clear."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"This could be planned as a 5 day training instead of 3, with more time on theory of modules and hands on exercises carried out in one single stretch. Because of the breaks in exercises, it was not easy to get the entire tool flow."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The interaction with trainers","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Development of a SWC from authoring to code generation could have been included.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Learning","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":" A good introduction training to AUTOSAR Classic. From absolute newbies to experienced AUTOSAR developers and integrators.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574652399240"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574652399240"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddb593884ed9c0017a73b5f"},"name":"Arun","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Saran Kumar","location":"TVS Motor- Bangalore","date":"2019-11-20 to 2019-11-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Theory part"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Theory part","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Demo on embedded target","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good training for AUTOSAR basics","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574656312107"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574656312107"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dde7661d6b7210017955d7c"},"name":"Rohit Yadav","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Akhil Raju,Saran Kumar","location":"TVS Motor- Bangalore","date":"2019-11-20 to 2019-11-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"Content was too much"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"It was confusing to understand the tool"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"Nice","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"They tried well to explain each queries","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"I feel it could have been in more easy way","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"good","trainerrating":[{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Saran Kumar","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Somewhat it helped to understand the basic. but implementation part was bit tough. It would be great if you can provide tutorial videos ."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Undestanding of concepts of AUTOSAR","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Implemenation on actual hardware","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"I am new this tool. i hope to learn it with your support.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"ECU programming","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes. i felt 3 days time was less. It would have been nice if it would have been covered in 4 days.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574860385518"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574860385518"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf4a0b0204970017d2f90c"},"name":"R. Priyanka","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Doing exercises based on concepts was most helpful"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"working on the tool and gaining knowledge","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Some of the topics which were in the PPT were missed","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 1/2 days","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Project purpose","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, but it would have been more helpful if we have worked some more days on tool so that we could have gained still more knowledge on configuration of tool.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574914571306"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574914571306"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf4b120204970017d2f90d"},"name":"Priyanka S","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"It was good. If some basic content is there then it will be even good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"EB tresos practice","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Some basic concepts is there then it will be good","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Not yet used","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574914834324"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574914834324"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf4b920204970017d2f90e"},"name":"Alagar","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"-"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"hands on experience in tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not worked on it","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"MCAL (Our team is using)","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574914962995"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574914962995"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf4c8b0204970017d2f90f"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"They are teaching very nice and explainations also good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The most valuable part is Comstack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Almost all topics are covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"I am new to this one","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Comstack, DEM","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"They are teaching very well. They are covering all topics. I am satisfied.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574915211562"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574915211562"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf4d190204970017d2f910"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"-"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Tool explaination","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No, Ididnt work previously","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Project purpose","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, but time is not sufficient to learn more. apart from that, everything is good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574915353337"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574915353337"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf4d7e0204970017d2f911"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Hands on the tools"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on the tools","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"CANOE, CAPL","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574915454921"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574915454921"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf57840204970017d2f912"},"name":"Nagarjuna N","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Setup installation is useful"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Practical exposure in tresos","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not worked","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Autosar","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Satisfied but require indepth training for better understanding of Autosar","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918020906"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918020906"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf583b0204970017d2f913"},"name":"Sunitha","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"EB tool explaination"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"EB tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No experience","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Autosar related project purpose","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, satisfied, the trainer was very good in explaining basic Autosar architecture and the EB tool and made us to work on the EB tool with his help.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918203768"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918203768"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf58b00204970017d2f914"},"name":"Chandrakala","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"EB tresos tool explaination"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"EB tresos tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"New to EB tresos","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Know about the new tool usage i.e EB tresos","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918320409"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918320409"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf592c0204970017d2f915"},"name":"Swathi M","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"-"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Explaining and hands on","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, but if this is a few more days I can get more experience in tool and understand it well","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918444805"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918444805"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf59e70204970017d2f917"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"yes"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM Stack, CAM, UDS all STD's","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No, all topics are covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"COM Stack, module topics (Project purpose)","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918631570"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918631570"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf5acc0204970017d2f918"},"name":"Apoorva U","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Yes, the explaination of step by step procedure is good and the document is also good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercise","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"maybe basic, who are new to autosar and automotive","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"To be used in future projects, not yet used","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918860679"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918860679"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf5b4e0204970017d2f919"},"name":"Manjunathagowda Hiregoudra","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"L&T Bangalore","date":"2019-11-06 to 2019-11-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Explaination and presentation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Presentation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes, satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918990267"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574918990267"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddf9beb8c78490017d5b43f"},"name":"SANJAYA K PANDA","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-11-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"cONTENT OF TRAINING"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"cONTENT OF TRAINING ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 Year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Cultural difference ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574935531009"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574935531009"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ddfaa0a07ce6a00171be9d6"},"name":"","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-11-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"It was a interactive session rather than theoretical."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The communication style, value track and usecase study were really informative.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"It would have better if some sensitive topics which should not be done are given more importance.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2.5 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, I had some good takeaways from the training and some of them are really helpful for building good relationship with counterparts.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1574939146460"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1574939146460"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de0a3bc025b2400174cd613"},"name":"Praveen N Nair","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-11-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"values for Germans,Dining etiquettes"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Understanding the culture","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Personal  & Family Values ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"11 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Interacting with OL2 or OL3 German Technical managers ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Great  & new learning, point of view on German Culture ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575003068941"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575003068941"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de0a429025b2400174cd614"},"name":"Budhdi Prakash Sharma","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-11-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I got to know about german culture."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"How to say no in sophisticated manner and how to greet.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not yet work on EB product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575003177710"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575003177710"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de0a9cf025b2400174cd615"},"name":"Bharath Byadgi","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-11-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"German values"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Saying NO in a diplomatic way ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No missing topics I would say","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2.6","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575004623273"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575004623273"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de0ac56025b2400174cd616"},"name":"","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-11-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Concrete details of the German culture was brought up."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Understanding and bridging the gap between the two different cultures.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. The training was really helpful to understand the culture and nature of Germans.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575005270242"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575005270242"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de0c6886ca25d001726f5f0"},"name":"","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-11-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Interaction with the participants"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Dining Etiquates and Saying no in softcorner","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"What we should not do or talk or not allowed to do in Geramany, as its also one most important part to understand their emotions.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":" 2 Years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Editing configuration files","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, training was good and was pretty much learned and yet to apply on works. \nOne suggestion would be to share the slides used in training as it will be used in future references, when ever we forgot or want to revise.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575011976304"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575011976304"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de103a2a144fa00177ad5f5"},"name":"","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-11-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":" "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":" NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":" NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":" yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575027618751"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575027618751"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de8a4f8dec47c0017761d20"},"name":"Rashmi B H","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-12-04 to 2019-12-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"All the sessions were good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All sessions","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Products and Finance","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 weeks","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Autosar","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes pretty much satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575527672158"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575527672158"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de8a57bdec47c0017761d21"},"name":"Abhinav Bhatnagar","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-12-04 to 2019-12-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked that most of the training sessions were short and explained core information required for day to day working."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Cab, cafeteria, org structure IT and info sec","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Not sure about that","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes! I am totally satisfied. I got an insight about culture at EB and how day to day operations happen. It will really help me to easily mix up in the organization.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575527803233"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575527803233"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de8af78dec47c0017761d22"},"name":"Gautham Chaubey","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-12-04 to 2019-12-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"They were very friendly and Clearing the doubts we get during session."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"To get know about our EB product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"EB Assist","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes ,Help to understand our organisation in better way.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575530360383"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575530360383"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de8c0ce6e206b0017a9c252"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-12-04 to 2019-12-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"QMS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All topics covered ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Open source software complaince ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575534798786"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575534798786"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de8c1696e206b0017a9c253"},"name":"Naresh K Katkar","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-12-04 to 2019-12-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"Good"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":"Good"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":"Good"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":"Good"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Interaction with the the employees."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Got to know transparency about the organization.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"i think it covered the all expected.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"MCAL Configuration at previous organization","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes. it was good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575534953483"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575534953483"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de8c3696e206b0017a9c254"},"name":"Tony Joseph","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-11-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"nothing"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"joke","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nothing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"EB treoss","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes i am satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575535465823"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575535465823"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de8c6a66e206b0017a9c255"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-12-04 to 2019-12-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"interaction"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"admin and Eb products ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"most of the task","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes, it is very useful with intraction with people","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575536294295"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575536294295"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de8c9e26e206b0017a9c256"},"name":"","training":"German Intercultural Training","trainers":"James","location":"EB IN","date":"2019-11-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"James","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"overall yes, may be more examples had to be given on how we interpret the german cultural differences"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Timing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"may be more examples had to be given on how we interpret the german cultural differences","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Meetings, During direct visit","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1575537122701"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1575537122701"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dfa0643e0eda500175861b6"},"name":"Archana Gondane","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Sasken, Pune","date":"2019-12-16 to 2019-12-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Understood the basic concepts and could relate with Practical use cases"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Slides and delivery of the content. Trainer has made sure to resolve the build error of each individual.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Almost all modules are covered. I wished if flashing hardware with hex file is also covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"POC project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Very much satisfied. Understood the Autosar module in depth.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1576666691827"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1576666691827"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dfa071ce0eda500175861b7"},"name":"Devendra ","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Sasken, Pune","date":"2019-12-16 to 2019-12-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Practical part should be more."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Praticals","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercise of safety, security, NM","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"POC","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Was expecting more of practical work.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1576666908034"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1576666908034"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dfa135c1f6a0100178f54d2"},"name":"Shubham Rokde","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Sasken, Pune","date":"2019-12-16 to 2019-12-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Need more assignment."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Timer configuration, Ethernet configuration, Flex ray configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW layer configuration.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"satisfied but need more hands on.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1576670044669"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1576670044669"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dfa256e1528ff00176147d1"},"name":"Yash Nichat","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Sasken, Pune","date":"2019-12-16 to 2019-12-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Need more hands-on on tool"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Most of the concepts are covered with proper thereotical understanding","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"hands on tool on ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW models configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. But training was little bit fast. Hands on tool was more expected. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1576674670902"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1576674670902"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dfa288b1528ff00176147d2"},"name":"Ajay Sanjay Yadav","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Sasken, Pune","date":"2019-12-16 to 2019-12-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Practical part should be more. That is some more exercise should be in training so things can be more clear."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on experience on tool.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Excercise for safety,security","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW layer configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Need more hands on practice while training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1576675467333"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1576675467333"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dfa29d31528ff00176147d3"},"name":"Akshay Langade","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Sasken, Pune","date":"2019-12-16 to 2019-12-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"More number of practicals should be covered, more exercises needed."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All the theorotical concepts. e.g. SWC, architecture of AUTOSAR","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Due to less time skipped Flexray, Ethernet and LIN protocol stacks.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuration of BSW layers.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Moderately satisfied, Missed some BSW stacks in training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1576675795770"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1576675795770"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dfa2a181528ff00176147d4"},"name":"Vaishali Janu Dhebe","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Sasken, Pune","date":"2019-12-16 to 2019-12-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Hands on practics"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"SWC and therotical parts","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"flexray,ethernet","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"configuration of BSW","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes but need more practical hands on tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1576675864639"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1576675864639"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dfa2c221528ff00176147d5"},"name":"Akshay Gajanan Gawande","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Sasken, Pune","date":"2019-12-16 to 2019-12-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":"More practicals should be there."},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Actually moderate but the practicals and the use cases should be more because you were not able to cover the most of the software."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Intrefacing of SWC to  RTE.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exploring of other communication modules e.g. Ethernet.etc.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW layer configuration.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Moderate, more number of test cases should be there.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1576676386503"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1576676386503"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dfaf86e0330540017d7b4e6"},"name":"Ganesh Jadhav","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Sasken, Pune","date":"2019-12-16 to 2019-12-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"satisfied, need more handson","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1576728686009"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1576728686009"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dfcb2b930203400176be36c"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","location":"Continental Bangalore","date":"2019-12-18 to 2019-12-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"Quality of the content was good"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":"Value of the content was good"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"Very good exercises but allocated time is not sufficient"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"needs improvement"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.67","comments":"presentation of SWC, RTE and Diagnostics topics need improvement","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.67","comments":"need improvement","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"need improvement","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.67","comments":"need improvement","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation of OS, Saftey and Com stack was super"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Presentation of OS, Saftey and Com stack was super","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"WC, RTE and Diagnostics topics need improvement","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuration of com stack and OS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":"good experience"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"good experience"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":"good experience"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"good experience"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"good experience","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1576841913611"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1576841913611"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e004f8256e3c1001739a74b"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","location":"Continental Bangalore","date":"2019-12-18 to 2019-12-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"no diagnostic exercise and also no SWC pacakge building excercise."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The RTE and SWC related content wee good ,"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"CAN stack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":" The excersie should be done live and not by having readily built file to import in EB.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Cluster applictaion software development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"The module experts need to be involved in training and not general set of two people who cannot explain all modules.\nAlso we need a more live handson, where we add a port or CAN message, instead of having readily importing System.arxml and solving erors.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1577078658806"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1577078658806"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e0056cd56e3c1001739a74c"},"name":"Azim","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","location":"Continental Bangalore","date":"2019-12-18 to 2019-12-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":"Needed more info on MCAL and Functional Safety concepts with respect to MCAL"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"EB tresos know how was good , but the steps could have been presented to us in a presentation for better understanding"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM stack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"MCAL ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For configuring OSEK scheduler tasks, DIO, etc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Overall the training was good , but could have been better with MCAL as well ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1577080525266"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1577080525266"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e005a6a56e3c1001739a74d"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","location":"Continental Bangalore","date":"2019-12-18 to 2019-12-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The training content was good . More time on hand On would be good . It was lil bit of rush at the end to complete the exersice . "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Communication Stack and OS concept was good . ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BswM ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"The trainer for part of RTE , SWC and Diagnostic was not able to share the knowledge in a better way ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1577081450507"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1577081450507"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e043cecab3f3500178e736c"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Anagha Govindjiwala,Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","location":"Continental Bangalore","date":"2019-12-18 to 2019-12-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Anagha Govindjiwala","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"practice session."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"practice session.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"generic autosar os concepts should be done better.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"autosar memory stack.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. It could be more beneficial if everything is in generic instead of taking example of CAN.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1577336044796"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1577336044796"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e16b4849a94f900171a17dc"},"name":"Ayush","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"perfectly planned sessions"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"session on tools (people strong, my EB plan, etc.)","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578546308169"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578546308169"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e16bb8c9a94f900171a17dd"},"name":"Nazareth Samson","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Everything","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 weeks","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Everything","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578548108771"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578548108771"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e16c1119a94f900171a17de"},"name":"Ashwini Patavardhan K V","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Sessions from Project heads and IT."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Sessions from the Project Heads","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Request you to accommodate  Demos from important projects. This gives more insight into the technical work done.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578549521568"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578549521568"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e16cd7246f8950017a64c10"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"-"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":"-"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"There weren't much excersises"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"-"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"understandable explaination, in detail."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":"-"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":"-"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":"-"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":"-"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578552690086"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578552690086"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e16cf3446f8950017a64c11"},"name":"Juffin Alex Varghese","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Got some overview on EB products and the way EB works"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Got the overview on EB and what different process followed and whom should contact in case of any support","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Demo on EB products","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, Thanks for giving this opportunity","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578553140757"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578553140757"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e16cf8546f8950017a64c12"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"Presentation from P.Lenin could be better","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"It was neither good nor bad. Improvements would be having good ppts. Hierarchy of promotion was not clearly understood. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"EB products and projects information section.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hierarchy of promotion was not clearly understood. Ans how to change the team if the present team is not given as per pre-employment discussions. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"3.5"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"As mentioned the following points can be considered -\n1) Presentation from P.Lenin could be better\n2) Hierarchy of promotion was not clearly understood\n3) How to change the team if the present team is not given as per pre-employment discussions","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578553221480"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578553221480"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e16d00b46f8950017a64c13"},"name":"Anshu Kumari","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Overall agenda got covered in short time and efficient manner."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Every part of the training is equally valuable.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Visualization of the EB's product (Short description)","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"10 days","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578553355823"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578553355823"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e16d14246f8950017a64c14"},"name":"Manuj Gupta","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Given the topics and duration of presentation, induction could have been compressed to one day. However, I am overall satisfied with the training. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578553666696"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578553666696"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e16d1f046f8950017a64c15"},"name":"Shibi Krishnamoorthy","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"About EB as a COmpany"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Different product of EB","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"11days","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"daily activities","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578553840305"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578553840305"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e16fb9ed757550017f80d69"},"name":"Prashant Mishra","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"Excellent"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":"Excellent"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":"Excellent"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":"Excellent"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"Excellent","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"Excellent","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"Excellent","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"Excellent","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"presentation by all"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"almost everything was good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"some products specific training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":"Nothing"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":"Good"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":"good"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":"Excellent"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It was really a great session where in short span we learnt about so many things.Really impressed.:)","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578564510667"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578564510667"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e170fc647ce17001723ccbf"},"name":"Venkat Saragada","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Comprehensive information with regard to Products & Projects and other facilities info which ever needed to a new joinee."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"QMS, Products, Projects and Finance overviews.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Information Security Overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578569670623"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578569670623"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e18375ca7a2b1001711987e"},"name":"Bhagyashri Patil","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-01-08 to 2020-01-09","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Transparency, Good knowledge about EB "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Most of the topics covered were good","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"List of things has to be done by new joinee. And Position hierarchy for engineers ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"HMI design","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":"QMS related topics could have been explained better, like how the scope in projects"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, Can be more interactive ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1578645340220"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1578645340220"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e43dca5f364e200175184a4"},"name":"","training":"Classic AUTOSAR (EB tresos)","trainers":"Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Shreedhar Baragi","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-02-10 to 2020-02-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NONE"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Classic Autosar Introduction","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Thanks","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581505701628"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581505701628"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e43f5f64300ec0017d67a12"},"name":"","training":"Classic AUTOSAR (EB tresos)","trainers":"Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Shreedhar Baragi","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-02-10 to 2020-02-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"basic conecpt of autosar"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"software component training ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Diagnostics hand on practice session","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"integartion ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581512182338"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581512182338"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e44c2b57e07c90017787922"},"name":"","training":"Classic AUTOSAR (EB tresos)","trainers":"Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Shreedhar Baragi","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-02-10 to 2020-02-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"need some more explanation with real time example"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"need more explanation with examples ","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"the AUTOSAR is the huge concept which can not be understand within span of time need more time to elaborate concepts "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"configuring the modules with hands on ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"i don not find","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"for OS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, as a fresher to the new concept like Autosar is the most probably met my requirement and i need to work more on it hope i am satisfied with training, possible kindly increase the quality and time for the same  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581564597955"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581564597955"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e44e59d220c9500175cac6b"},"name":"Faizur Rahman Nizar Ali","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2020-02-12 to 2020-02-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"I am bit new to Automative domain. But It's quite interesting to know the terminologies, product concepts and to incorporates with my Devops role  in parallel."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Corporate Overview"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Elektrobit Vision & Mission is up to the mark and consistent improvement","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Everything is covered except Products Overview topic which has been postponed to 19th Feb 2020.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"With in a month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Devops CI & CD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes I am satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581573533616"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581573533616"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e452530e5bdf30017cc65d5"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2020-02-12 to 2020-02-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"It gave good overview about the future plans "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Projects Overview and QMS Overview was most valuable ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I thing they covered every thing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Just 1 week old","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For configuration and  integration.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yeah! , It gave good overview of the companies motive. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581589808315"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581589808315"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e452ee4e5bdf30017cc65d6"},"name":"Ekta Pandey","training":"Classic AUTOSAR (EB tresos)","trainers":"Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Shreedhar Baragi","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-02-10 to 2020-02-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The training helped to gain better understanding of all the main modules of AUTOSAR"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercises","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"For Diag module, exercise was not done, only theorotical part was covered.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years 3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Bootloader Development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, The training was really helpful. \nSuggestion: Extend the duration from 3 days to 4-5 days. Along with the therotical knowledge , hands on is also important so as to easily relate the topic. But due to time constraints, we could not do all the exercises. Also, for Diag module, no hands on was done.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581592292230"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581592292230"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e4617ac53d89a0017afe28c"},"name":"MARUTHI H","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2020-02-12 to 2020-02-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Content of the training"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Projects Overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"...","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581651884750"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581651884750"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e46311953d89a0017afe28e"},"name":"","training":"Classic AUTOSAR (EB tresos)","trainers":"Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Shreedhar Baragi","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-02-10 to 2020-02-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Hands on"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"If we could create own work space instead of importing the existing work space the understanding would be better.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"New joinee","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Yet to use","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes Satisfied. The training would have been more better if the number of days were more for training as I am new to Autosar.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581658393159"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581658393159"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e4634e553d89a0017afe28f"},"name":"L bhargavi Reddy","training":"Classic AUTOSAR (EB tresos)","trainers":"Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Shreedhar Baragi","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-02-10 to 2020-02-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Time was taken for explaining doubts with examples"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No experience","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Bootloader","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581659365002"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581659365002"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e46388853d89a0017afe290"},"name":"","training":"Classic AUTOSAR (EB tresos)","trainers":"Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Shreedhar Baragi","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-02-10 to 2020-02-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Topics covered and agenda is clear and good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Practical exercises","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training is good..bit tight schedule for to cover all the topics and practical exercises.training can be extended to one more day so that schedule could be rush free.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581660296079"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581660296079"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e465a00ef17060017fec60d"},"name":"AJITH S S","training":"Classic AUTOSAR (EB tresos)","trainers":"Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Shreedhar Baragi","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-02-10 to 2020-02-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The training was good. But due time contraints I could not finish the excercises. The reason, as this training for new joinees and few of them were new to AUTOSAR , there were lots of doubts and its takes extra time to answe tthose questions "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Demo session was good and the way how trainers answered the doubts also good","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, But I felt 3 days not sufficient","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581668864783"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581668864783"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e4a26bc7cb7c40017d6ed4c"},"name":"","training":"Classic AUTOSAR (EB tresos)","trainers":"Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Shreedhar Baragi","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-02-10 to 2020-02-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Exercise"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"CAN stack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"DETAILED COM STACK","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2YRS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"CAN AND MEMSTACK FOR BL","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"YES","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581917884262"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581917884262"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e4a398435db1c001714c723"},"name":"Naresk Katkar","training":"Classic AUTOSAR (EB tresos)","trainers":"Vijayan Thangavel,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Shreedhar Baragi","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-02-10 to 2020-02-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Shreedhar Baragi","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"concepts picked for the training,"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercise","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Detail concept about mode managment(BSWM, COMM)","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"MCAL  and BSW integration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes, for beginners it is helpfull.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1581922692156"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1581922692156"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e4e2d02a480480017ff443b"},"name":"SONA BABU","training":"Java(Basics)","trainers":"Ravi Rathod","location":"Board Room","date":"2020-04-12 to 2020-02-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The way of presenting and the contents and examples"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The examples and exercise","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Multi threading, Collections, Advanced JAVA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training is good. But some contents are missing like threads and collections. Please include them as well in future similar trainings","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1582181634555"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1582181634555"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e4e2e76a480480017ff443c"},"name":"","training":"Java(Basics)","trainers":"Ravi Rathod","location":"Board Room","date":"2020-04-12 to 2020-02-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"OOPs connecpt "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Got a basic understanding on JAVA.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More hands on training needed","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"4monthd","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Project purpose","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"More hands on training needed.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1582182006165"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1582182006165"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e54d50e964baa00170a6606"},"name":"Sreedevi H R","training":"Java(Basics)","trainers":"Ravi Rathod","location":"Board Room","date":"2020-04-12 to 2020-02-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation and theoretical example explanation was good "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Java OOPS concepts","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Would like to work out the concepts with more examples","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"writing the test scripts","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training was organized/planned in a well manner. Coverage of concepts was excellent. \n","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1582617870549"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1582617870549"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e54ddf7964baa00170a6607"},"name":"M Mahidhar Reddy","training":"Java(Basics)","trainers":"Ravi Rathod","location":"Board Room","date":"2020-04-12 to 2020-02-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Exercises"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"OOPS concept","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"almost every topic covered ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"so far i didnt use it anywhere in the product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Quite satisfied with the content and interaction","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1582620151240"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1582620151240"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e563101f36e0b00174dd98c"},"name":"MANJUNATH NANDIKOL","training":"Java(Basics)","trainers":"Ravi Rathod","location":"Board Room","date":"2020-04-12 to 2020-02-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ravi Rathod","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Basic of JAVA and oops concepts "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"oops concepts in java","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on programme's ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes satisfied with the training. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1582706945712"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1582706945712"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e57a97b508a5f00179a1f16"},"name":"Ravindra","training":"Automotive Ethernet (AR Ethernet stack)","trainers":"Thekkedathu, George","location":"Skype ","date":"2020-02-27","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"content"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"configuration overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Testing part","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"ICAS project Testability services","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"training was good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1582803323467"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1582803323467"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e57ac1d508a5f00179a1f17"},"name":"","training":"Automotive Ethernet (AR Ethernet stack)","trainers":"Thekkedathu, George","location":"Skype ","date":"2020-02-27","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"pdu multiplexing and SD usage"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"SOMEIP-SD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"5 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"SOMEIP configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes Satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1582803997286"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1582803997286"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e589cb1d56ab70017dcfbbc"},"name":"","training":"Automotive Ethernet (AR Ethernet stack)","trainers":"Thekkedathu, George","location":"Skype ","date":"2020-02-27","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Thekkedathu, George","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The trainer was precise in the content that he planned to deliver and executed perfectly"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The contents","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"PIP","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. It was useful to understand the service oriented communication better.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1582865585617"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1582865585617"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e60969e41f2f40017f3e68d"},"name":"Shrungar Ghormare","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-03-04 to 2020-03-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Structured training Content","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All topics are covered.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Around a month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Project Purpose ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes,Clearly explained Induction topics.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1583388318098"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1583388318098"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e6096f241f2f40017f3e68e"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-03-04 to 2020-03-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The topics were presented very well"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All the information provided","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1583388402844"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1583388402844"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e60974841f2f40017f3e68f"},"name":"Bhargavi Reddy","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-03-04 to 2020-03-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"interactive sessions "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Required topics where covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"one month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Bootloader","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1583388488522"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1583388488522"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e60a06641f2f40017f3e690"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-03-04 to 2020-03-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation was upto the mark and interactive"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All the sessions were important","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nothing noticied","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Daily","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training was well organized. Mandatory for the new joinee","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1583390822133"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1583390822133"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e66f6885906760017eeb306"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-03-04 to 2020-03-05","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"most liked is environment but need buddy process so that it could be very easy to understand the company very well soon"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"every thing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"every thing is covered hope so","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BL","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes i am satisfied with training ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1583806088552"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1583806088552"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5e6eef36f91f5200171f70d0"},"name":"","training":"ITA (Testing Tool)","trainers":"Ande Adinarayana,Saba Nikhath","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-03-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"2.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ande Adinarayana","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Saba Nikhath","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ande Adinarayana","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Saba Nikhath","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ande Adinarayana","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Saba Nikhath","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Ande Adinarayana","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Saba Nikhath","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"More Hands on experience should have been done."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Content","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More Hands on experience","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"unit testing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1584328502378"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1584328502378"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eafff256d0f4d00171d05e6"},"name":"Rangegowda R","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"-"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Introduction part","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1588592421678"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1588592421678"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eb002ad6d0f4d00171d05e7"},"name":"Gajendra Veeranna","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Clear explanation of policies "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Explanation of insurance policies","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have added more information on new and old tax regime.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 weeks","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"HRMS related updates and information","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes satisfied with the training, neatly presented by the trainer.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1588593325571"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1588593325571"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eb00b886d0f4d00171d05e8"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Interaction with all the employees."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"About the EB values and HR policies","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing all were covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"11 days","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Good","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1588595592139"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1588595592139"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eb26a41d848bf00172d70c6"},"name":"Sanjeev Kulkarni","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"content of presentation was good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"stated with introduction , company mission","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"information about FBP, and other EB India specific information. But  I think it will be covered in other trainings","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"AUTOSAR development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, training was interactive and knowledgeable. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1588750913790"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1588750913790"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eb3cc2b8e5042001725b221"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I was expecting it to have a brief introduction about Elektrobit and this session had that."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Presentation about the Elektrobit and its policies","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Not, really.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1588841515079"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1588841515079"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eb429b0be1a2f00173251e9"},"name":"Abhilash M","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the way the session was presented and the way it was carried till the end"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Information","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"very satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1588865456302"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1588865456302"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eb437d748302900178b2a79"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Overall the explanation by HR team is satisfied. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Details about Insurance","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I didnot find anything such like","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Did not get this question!!","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":" Entire training was good with required information like details of insurance, leave policies etc..","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1588869079520"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1588869079520"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eb44fe2963229001773bc38"},"name":"vikash pandey","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Every thing was very good, we get to know about a lot of thing such as policies and work culture."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Information about different policies and information regarding use of tools such as AAV time sheet etc.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes I am very satisfied with the training, thanks to Hr Team for organizing this informative session.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1588875234918"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1588875234918"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eb508274292960017659754"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Amid of corona outbreak,conducting an induction and having us onboard -we are really grateful for that."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Right from introduction to the policies,tools and all about Elektrobit was rightly told.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All the necessary topics were covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"It's been a month now.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Wherever applicable","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1588922407034"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1588922407034"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eb50eb64292960017659755"},"name":"Umesh Hiremath","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"It was interactive session"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Over view of org","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Tools to be aquented to work in EN","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Joined last week","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Dev","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, it was well structured to welcome new member into the EB Family","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1588924086923"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1588924086923"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eb8d4af33862a00177eccbb"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-04-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The content was very user friendly, interactive, with all the relevant information, and the question were listened to and answered"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"user friendly, interactive, with all the relevant information, and the question were listened to and answered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Most of the relevant topics were covered.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For day to day activities","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, the training was good with required information","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1589171375771"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1589171375771"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ec23f9afc35ae001721140c"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-05-11 to 2020-05-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"For the hands-on part, it would've been a little better if the presentation had gone a bit slower.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"For the most part, I was very satisfied of the comprehensiveness of the training."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Both of the theoretical and practical parts.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Not that I can think of at the moment.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1.5 year and I'm new to both software engineering field and AUTOSAR field.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For the most part, following up the customer issues. Sometimes relevant projects.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"I am satisfied with the training. Big thanks to both of the trainers for the structured and comprehensive training. I was able to make concrete some of the unclear knowledge about AUTOSAR and I'm now better equipped with EB tresos Studio configuration skills as well.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1589788570626"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1589788570626"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ec24084fc35ae001721140d"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-05-11 to 2020-05-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"OS and Exercise"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Safety and Security","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"exercise about FIM, Safety and Security","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"over an year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"to support a customers","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Thank you for your kind training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1589788804276"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1589788804276"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ec24134fc35ae001721140e"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Vijayan Thangavel","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-05-11 to 2020-05-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I can learn whole basic AUTOSAR system with tresos hand-on training. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Tips when tresos does not work properly. (like closing project and reopen)","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"If OTA is added then it would be good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"about a month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"To support customer about tresos studio and ACP","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"I am fully satisfied this training.\n\n","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1589788980113"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1589788980113"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ec4f7adb7a1040017e0b157"},"name":"Sanjeev Kulkarni","training":"C++ Basics and Intermediate","trainers":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-15 to 2020-05-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"because of lack of time, could not able to take more exercise"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"training matarials"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Training was very useful for beginners, covered from scrach","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"covered most of the topics","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"for EB product development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"YES!!. It will be more fruitfull if given more time(more than 18hrs) for the training ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1589966765623"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1589966765623"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ec4fb12b7a1040017e0b158"},"name":"areef","training":"C++ Basics and Intermediate","trainers":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-15 to 2020-05-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"presenting the concepts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"learning the concepts i dont know","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"almost everything is covered ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"for about an year working on EB corbos","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"for applications for the adaptive autosar","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes it is very useful ,content with example code is useful","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1589967634457"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1589967634457"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ec4fd86b7a1040017e0b159"},"name":"Rosmy","training":"C++ Basics and Intermediate","trainers":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-15 to 2020-05-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"upcoming projects","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1589968262258"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1589968262258"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ec50221b7a1040017e0b15a"},"name":"Rangegowda","training":"C++ Basics and Intermediate","trainers":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-15 to 2020-05-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Prsentation and explanation about the concepts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1589969441763"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1589969441763"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ec50305b7a1040017e0b15b"},"name":"Mohit Aphale","training":"C++ Basics and Intermediate","trainers":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-15 to 2020-05-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The training content. Theory + practical coding."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The best part of training was Suresh was very interactive. he was actually solving question with us and also provided lot of very basic concepts. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"N/A","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"20 Days","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Learn C++ and then write exploits. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. I am satisfied. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1589969669104"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1589969669104"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ec507c6b7a1040017e0b15c"},"name":"Harish Kumar Nayak","training":"Jenkins  Basics & Intermediate","trainers":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"Contents are very good."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":"Useful for my implementation.\n"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"NA"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The Ideas of Implementation to my Project."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The DEMOs","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"5month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For continuous Integration to all all PIP projects. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Over all a nice learning.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1589970886715"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1589970886715"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ec63676e3d149001718caea"},"name":"","training":"C++ Basics and Intermediate","trainers":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-15 to 2020-05-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jagadeeshaiah, Suresh","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The in-depth understanding of concepts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"object oriented concepts","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"topics were covered but it would be more better if more time was allocated for training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year 2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Adaptive Autosar reference applications","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"The topics needed more time than 8 hours for the better understanding. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1590048374317"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1590048374317"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed0b6cb060d9400172aa8ba"},"name":"","training":"Adaptive AUTOSAR (EB corbos) ","trainers":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ,Annadurai, Anbarasan ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-26 to 2020-05-29","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"overall training was ok"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"demo sessions","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"basics were coverd","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"zero","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736587572"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736587572"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f058f87f8781200175c809f"},"name":"Amarnath","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan,Vijayan Thangavel,Swapnil Langarkande,Aravind L","location":"Online","date":"2020-07-01 to 2020-07-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.83","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Got basic idea to use  eb tool"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Final day training connecting all dots. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Na","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1594199943764"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1594199943764"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f15824c0477b10017de09aa"},"name":"Pooja Patil","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti - Online","date":"2020-07-06 to 2020-07-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Explaination and answered all most all the questions which we had."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Explanation of configuration parameter","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3Years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuration of BSW and MCAL modules","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245132103"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245132103"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f1582a80477b10017de09ab"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti - Online","date":"2020-07-06 to 2020-07-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Nice explanation "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Com stack, CAN stack and diagnostics ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"SPI training but it told that trainer is not available","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good training with nice explanations on the topic ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245224577"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245224577"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f1582ac0477b10017de09ac"},"name":"Raghavendra Kariyannavar","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti - Online","date":"2020-07-06 to 2020-07-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I understood CAN communication and UDS part and I could not get E2E part"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Communication stack for CAN and UDS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM and E2E","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Recently strated","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW modules","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245228416"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245228416"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f1583160477b10017de09ad"},"name":"Geetha T R","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti - Online","date":"2020-07-06 to 2020-07-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"quality of content is good. in Some of documents only flowchart is given. description is less"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":"Good"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"There was time limitation for hands on configuration"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"Good"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presenation and explanation of Comstack basics"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"mode management and Comstack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW confguration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes..","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245334621"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245334621"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f15834a0477b10017de09ae"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti - Online","date":"2020-07-06 to 2020-07-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"Content was good. Understandable"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"Hands on was quite less."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Comstack and Diagnostic topics"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Comstack and DCM was good session for me","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"CANFD, DET, and hands-on for all topics","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 - Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"DAF Project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Overall Good. Productive session.. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245386765"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245386765"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f15841e0477b10017de09af"},"name":"Seenivasan","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti - Online","date":"2020-07-06 to 2020-07-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Yes, explained about all the layers and modules in the autosar"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"how to do manual configuration in EB Tresos ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More then arxml configuration. need to do manual configuration for all modules in EB Tresos ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"DAF","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes i was useful. Also need more manual configuration and hands on ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245598760"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245598760"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f1584550477b10017de09b0"},"name":"Manasa Basavaraju","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Conti - Online","date":"2020-07-06 to 2020-07-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"3","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"way of explanation."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Can ,Mode Management and Diagngostics.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"J1939 (Configuration)and CDD ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Configuartion.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"4"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.., it was good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245653010"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595245653010"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2919dbc67e2700174e7d0a"},"name":"Lokesh U","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Explained where we can find training materials and other pdf"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"scripts","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exception handlings","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3+","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"debugging","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596529115464"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596529115464"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2b9af63797e70017b30376"},"name":"MADHUSUDHAN A S","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"presenation skill and real time examples"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Cmm scripts training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Trainer will show the operation in simulator if it is on real time hardware it will be good","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"debugging","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693238031"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693238031"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2b9b303797e70017b30377"},"name":"","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"More awareness on tool"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"knowng scripts to use tool","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Debugging","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes It is informative.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693296677"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693296677"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed0b6cf060d9400172aa8bb"},"name":"","training":"Adaptive AUTOSAR (EB corbos) ","trainers":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ,Annadurai, Anbarasan ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-26 to 2020-05-29","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The flow of training and training material"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"excise part","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"covered all most for basic","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"zero","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736591023"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736591023"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed0b6cf060d9400172aa8bc"},"name":"Himanshu Malviya","training":"Adaptive AUTOSAR (EB corbos) ","trainers":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ,Annadurai, Anbarasan ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-26 to 2020-05-29","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Properly explained"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercise part ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"As i have less knowledge about adaptive so i have less idea what actually was missing. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For perssonal knowledge.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yeah . As an introduction to a new platform, it was good to attend this training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736591626"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736591626"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed0b74e060d9400172aa8bd"},"name":"","training":"Adaptive AUTOSAR (EB corbos) ","trainers":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ,Annadurai, Anbarasan ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-26 to 2020-05-29","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"4"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4\n4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4\n4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"4\n4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"4\n4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Exercise "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Starterkit architecture and container concept, Adaptive Autosar architecture","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Corbos product support","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"4"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training was good enough to understand Adaptive Autosar overview and its applications. Usage of Starterkit \nTrainers had a good knowledge about the product and delivered the training very comprehensive way. So that participants could follow easily","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736718953"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736718953"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed0b7c1060d9400172aa8be"},"name":"Imazuddin Shaik","training":"Adaptive AUTOSAR (EB corbos) ","trainers":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ,Annadurai, Anbarasan ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-26 to 2020-05-29","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The content planned for training is very good. It covers all the basic concepts. Hands-on gave more undersanding of concepts."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Architecture info and Hand-on","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"It looks good for me.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"I'm new to EB corbos ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"No plan yet. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, Satisfied. It would be more interactive if it face to face.\nThe training went litter faster, I feel the planned time for this training is less. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736833799"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736833799"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed0b7fe060d9400172aa8bf"},"name":"Murali CM","training":"Adaptive AUTOSAR (EB corbos) ","trainers":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ,Annadurai, Anbarasan ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-26 to 2020-05-29","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Hands on was good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on with excersizes","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"For Introductory overview it is okay otherwise internal logical view of each functional cluster with implementation perspective is expected.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Demo applications","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"it was a good session overall for an Introduction.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736894273"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1590736894273"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed487369ba50e00170fd06c"},"name":"Abhilash M","training":"Adaptive AUTOSAR (EB corbos) ","trainers":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ,Annadurai, Anbarasan ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-26 to 2020-05-29","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The overview of the Adaptive AutoSAr and how to write a simple application in EB corbos Studio"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Theory and Practiacal","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2.5 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"All the components explained in the session will help me understand the system better and there by write better integration test cases","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Very satisfied with the training","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1590986550702"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1590986550702"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed4a3a4e4012f001723a19b"},"name":"","training":"Adaptive AUTOSAR (EB corbos) ","trainers":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ,Annadurai, Anbarasan ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-26 to 2020-05-29","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"1.50","comments":"fluency in the delivering the training was missing.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"1"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"1.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"1"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"introduction and overview"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Persistency Management","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No comments","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"linux ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":"Need fluency while delivering the training. "},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1590993828013"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1590993828013"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed7220a3d47cb00179fda3a"},"name":"Abhilash M","training":"Jenkins  Basics & Intermediate","trainers":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the way the session was presented and the way it was carried till the end"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Jenkins scheduling","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Daily execution of builds","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"very satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591157258586"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591157258586"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed722b33d47cb00179fda3b"},"name":"","training":"Jenkins  Basics & Intermediate","trainers":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Explanation with examples"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"parameters explanation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"pipeline","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"continuous integration builds for icas1","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Very useful one. Expecting training about pipelines with examples in jenkins","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591157427146"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591157427146"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed73e8464315500179fae12"},"name":"","training":"Jenkins  Basics & Intermediate","trainers":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Krishnamoorthy, Shibi﻿ ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Yes to an extent but need handson with daily activities"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The Jenkins config","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2YRS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BL configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591164548810"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591164548810"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed74a96887dcf0017ed3c35"},"name":"Kavyashree B.E","training":"Adaptive AUTOSAR (EB corbos) ","trainers":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ,Annadurai, Anbarasan ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-05-26 to 2020-05-29","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"They managed to bring in multiple topics in stipulated time"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":"Basic knowledge on the topic."},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Hussaini, Syed Abrar ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Annadurai, Anbarasan ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The way trainer was interacting with people,its was more of 2 way communication."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Theoritical session way more informative for non adaptive autosar people as well","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing as per my knowledge","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"I use for integration purpose","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591167638864"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591167638864"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed79f5c11428000172d4324"},"name":"Abhilash M","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2020-05-11 to 2020-05-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the way the session was presented and the way it was carried till the end"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All the information were valuable","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591189340246"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591189340246"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed79fc411428000172d4325"},"name":"Gajendra Veeranna","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2020-05-11 to 2020-05-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":".","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591189444205"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591189444205"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed7b7111f1d13001748dfe6"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2020-05-11 to 2020-05-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Having an induction held amid of the corona outbreak,we are really grateful for that"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Everything","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All necessary topics were covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Wherever applicable","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591195409539"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591195409539"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed8711ad7b92d00176d8cd2"},"name":"Sanjeev Kulkarni","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2020-05-11 to 2020-05-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"training covered most of the topics. good to know about it"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"training Contents","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"1. I was expected to know about FPB, like how to claim, what are the documents necessary etc, which was missing in the training 2. it is better to include some basic EB product related info 3. In finance, if tax related information is added, then it is relally useful","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"for EB product development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"I am satisfied with the training. I have few comments\n1. I was expected to know about FPB, like how to claim, what are the documents necessary etc, which was missing in the training\n2. it is better to include some basic EB product related info\n3. In finance, if tax related information is added, then it is relally useful\n","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591243034786"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591243034786"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed8931b2e2c3d00179ded85"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2020-05-11 to 2020-05-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":" "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":" ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591251739200"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591251739200"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ed933d45566a000178fb4f2"},"name":"vikash pandey","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2020-05-11 to 2020-05-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Everything was very good"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All parts were good as they provided valuable information regarding different processes","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, those were very informative sessions","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591292884373"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591292884373"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ede0f5bfcb8af001714353b"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"HR IN","location":"EB IN","date":"2020-05-11 to 2020-05-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"HR IN","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591611227702"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591611227702"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ee315936fa6750017b58aac"},"name":"","training":"C++14 Intermediate and Advanced","trainers":"Shobha Bhardwaj","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-11 to 2020-06-12","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shobha Bhardwaj","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"Topics are covered too fast, even before a sentence is understood, the next sentence is thrown out. I think the instructor is in a lot of hurry. ","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shobha Bhardwaj","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shobha Bhardwaj","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shobha Bhardwaj","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The object oriented concepts are to be explained with more detail. We will need more examples. Designs can be more explained in details."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Inheritance ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Easier explanations","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Designs and programming","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Not satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1591940499316"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1591940499316"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eeb0b388a914b0017241f47"},"name":"Renuka Pujar","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"good understanding of the topic"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592462136802"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592462136802"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eeb0b678a914b0017241f48"},"name":"Ashwini K V P","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"System Bus and interrupt handlers"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"IPC and Threading","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"PASA architecture","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"More than 5 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"My project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":"If project requires QNX internals"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":"in day to day project"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Very good !!!","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592462183000"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592462183000"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eeb0d1d8a914b0017241f49"},"name":"Indrayani Kamat","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Got better understanding on QNX architecture which will be useful to solve crash issues."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"indetail explanation of threads , processes and the communication between them.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The basics of QNX Architecture was covered. Requesting to have a session on  PASA framework. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes . Thank you Kishore and Ranjit for the session.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592462621966"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592462621966"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eeb0ee02b195b00173d0670"},"name":"","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Detailing of the concept and the way of answering was good."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Content of the Presentation was good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592463072757"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592463072757"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eeb118e2b195b00173d0671"},"name":"Pallavi Bandak","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The QNX overview explanation "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Understanding of difference between QNX,LInux","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More explanation on multicore topic","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592463758390"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592463758390"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eeb15cd2b195b00173d0672"},"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"NA as there was no exercise"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"2.00","comments":"NA for Ranjit Katuri as only kishore presented the content","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"1"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"NA for Ranjit Katuri as only kishore presented the content","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"1"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"introduction and overview"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Process and prioritization ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"how the messages are exchanged between 2 systems","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592464845200"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592464845200"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eeb23db07225900178cb79a"},"name":"Prabhat Nayak","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"In Depth coverage of the contents in the simplest way possible"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All contents were of equal weight-age in understanding the complete picture.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years 3  months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Our infotainment product has QNX as OS. So almost for all the task like crash analysis, CPU/resource  usage etc  knowledge of QNX is useful","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Totally satisfied.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592468443081"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592468443081"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eec4f8fd7e78f001765523e"},"name":"","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Content was very deep and informative. Well communicated."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Interrupts handling and the content. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Most of the topics covered. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"more than a year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"We use this for our project.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes the session was very informative and useful for the project. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592545167313"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592545167313"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eec534cd7e78f001765523f"},"name":"","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Session was very informative . The way contents are presented was easy to understand ."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All the part was equally important.  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I would want to attend mentioned topics 1. Pasa FW PasApplication 2. Pasa Timers 3. Sync Startup & Shutdown power modes 4. Remote debugging using QNX Momentics 5. QNX System profiling using tracelogger & Momentics","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Till now I did not get chance to work with EB product. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"I am working in Ford project where we are not using EB product. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"I am very satisfied with the training . Would like to attend \n1. Pasa FW PasApplication\n2. Pasa Timers\n3. Sync Startup & Shutdown power modes\n4. Remote debugging using QNX Momentics\n5. QNX System profiling using tracelogger & Momentics.\n\nThank you so much Kishore and Ranjit for such a nice session.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592546124784"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592546124784"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eec64679d04390017c31748"},"name":"","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592550503811"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592550503811"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eec64d89d04390017c31749"},"name":"","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"scheduling"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"scheduler","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nothing as per my knowledge","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"12","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"build","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592550616954"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592550616954"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eec6a8e9d04390017c3174a"},"name":"","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Need to give more clarification about QNX architecture."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"QNX architecture ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"New project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Got the exposure about QNX platform. Need to give the more explanation with one example how it works really and how it differs from other platforms.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592552078760"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592552078760"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eec7476b10cd80017df5ef4"},"name":"Nitheesh","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Covering the Qnx topics from the basics was advantageous "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Kernel and Scheduler topics","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Day to day work","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592554614579"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592554614579"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef1cf4d70d162001710365d"},"name":"Shweta Adarsh Jogur","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-23","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"evrything explained neatly"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Insurance","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"all explained","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not yet","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"not yet used","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592905549311"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592905549311"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef1cf7070d162001710365e"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-23","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"EB vision"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Links to infohub","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"MEPL","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"AAV TimeSheets, PeopleStrong","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. But we were not able to session within given time slot","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592905584976"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592905584976"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef1d11470d162001710365f"},"name":"Tejaswi Henjarappa H S","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-23","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Career paths"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"HR policies","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Food and transport facility","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For day to day activities","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Covered all the HR policies, employee benefits, career paths etc.\n","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592906004331"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592906004331"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef1d35170d1620017103660"},"name":"","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-23","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Time was not enough"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Benefits ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Payroll related, How to fill FBP etc and NPS","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"General","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592906577225"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592906577225"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef1d43970d1620017103661"},"name":"Deepak Kumar","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-23","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"whole training"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"whole training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"I am not aware","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"right now, not aware","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Thank you Vidhya for valuable training, it will be helpful for me.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592906809743"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592906809743"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef1d7d270d1620017103662"},"name":"Muniraj","training":"Induction","trainers":"Vidhya Rani","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-23","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Vidhya Rani","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Interaction with the team members"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Clarification on isurance policies","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1592907730871"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1592907730871"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef340ce8805610017b87a10"},"name":"Amarnath","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Examples and the handson"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All the handson","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"_","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000142050"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000142050"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef340f98805610017b87a11"},"name":"","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Good : Reviewing the contents of other team's work. Improvement :The network connectivity of the trainer was poor and affected the quality of training."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Word Usage and Grammatical Part of language in Paper writing.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Flow could have been improved","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"The network connectivity of the trainer was poor and affected the quality of training.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000185551"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000185551"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef341078805610017b87a12"},"name":"RISHIKA VISHWAKARMA","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"All the contents are well enough."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The activities","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing such, just time line was less. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"approx 3.4years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For report writing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000199708"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000199708"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef3413c8805610017b87a13"},"name":"Sona Babu","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The trainer was making participants do the exercises which is more effective"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercises","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":"Network issues were there"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000252865"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000252865"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef3415a8805610017b87a14"},"name":"","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Clear communication"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Structure of a report","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Topics were not missing, but could have provided more time for each section, also there were network issues.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Paper Presentation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, but need more time for all the topics","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000282009"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000282009"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef341678805610017b87a15"},"name":"Hari Babu","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Too basics, would have been more matured contents in comparison with previous technical papers for example."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Some what.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"To add maturity to submit paper at global level","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1.6 yrs","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"tooling solutions","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Not exactly","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000295501"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000295501"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef3417a8805610017b87a16"},"name":"","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"IT WAS MORE OF GRAMMAR, I DONT KNOW , ONLY LOOKED LIKE FEW USEFUL SKILL/THINGS LEARNED.  CONTENT COULD Have been better."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"The structure of Report","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Expected a bit more, maybe she taking up a topic and going on to write with us","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"4yrs","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"source code Generation ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Not satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000314841"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000314841"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef341af8805610017b87a17"},"name":"Sinu Isac","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"we wrote a sample paper in the workshop"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"sttory lines","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"i do not know","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Integation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, satisfied. But due to the network issues tend to miss certain points.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000367258"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000367258"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef341b18805610017b87a18"},"name":"Chinmayi G","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Activities of making us write the report and review."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Process of writing a report","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Nothing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Writing paper","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, the start of the event could have been more energetic, it was a nice to introduce ourselves but post that 1 hour felt low in energy.\nWhen activities were there it was interesting.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000369168"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000369168"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef341b98805610017b87a19"},"name":"","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Team activities were good "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Got to know what needs to be taken care when you are preparing for a paper presentaion ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"everything covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Will be taking care when we prepare for the paper presentation ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes,\n","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000377073"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000377073"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef341cf8805610017b87a1a"},"name":"Tejaswi Henjarappa H S","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Content writing structure"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Checklist ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"E-Horizon","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Training has met the basic structure of content writing and required grammar corrections. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000399130"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000399130"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef341d08805610017b87a1b"},"name":"Indu","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The structure of the training"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"the group exercises enabling the team to share each others view points","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Not sure if there were any","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"paper presentation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000400254"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000400254"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef341d88805610017b87a1c"},"name":"","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"should be More relevant to technical paper"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"5 Question session","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"its not much  specific to technical writing ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Paper writing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Excepted more so not satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000408827"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000408827"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef341d98805610017b87a1d"},"name":"","training":"Technical Storytelling","trainers":"Shoba Peters","location":"MS Teams","date":"2020-06-24","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"GOOD"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":"GOOD"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"GOOD"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"GOOD"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"GOOD","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"GOOD","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"GOOD","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"GOOD","trainerrating":[{"name":"Shoba Peters","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"activities planned"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Writing own paper and reviewing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Trainer should have reviwed our containt in front of us","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"All","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000409879"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593000409879"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ef485c53ea866001791c0a8"},"name":"Tarun Trivedi","training":"QNX","trainers":"Katuri Ranjit,Arepalli Kishore","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-06-18","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Katuri Ranjit","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Arepalli Kishore","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Getting more insight of the QNX."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All the basics that will to narrow down the approaches in future.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1593083333899"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1593083333899"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f059354f8781200175c80a0"},"name":"Rahul K R","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan,Vijayan Thangavel,Swapnil Langarkande,Aravind L","location":"Online","date":"2020-07-01 to 2020-07-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.83","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The hands on sessions can be more interactive and invest extra time for the same"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Tool explanation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Examples touching the configuration of Mem-Stack. Giving assignments and evaluating","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"First time","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"AutoSAR project development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"The training sessions were so good and informative. But because of the online platform, the interaction was not so effective.\nExtra time can be allotted for Hands-on sessions.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1594200916889"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1594200916889"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f05ade53788d3001728317e"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan,Vijayan Thangavel,Swapnil Langarkande,Aravind L","location":"Online","date":"2020-07-01 to 2020-07-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"explanation of different modules"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"presentation of topic and practical","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"A little bit of exercise is included that will be good","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"This is first time.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"We focuses on Application side","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Overall the training is good. But at end of each session it goes in fast pace which need to be avoided.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1594207717974"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1594207717974"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f05b8198c22d6001763f29c"},"name":"SREENI T S","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan,Vijayan Thangavel,Swapnil Langarkande,Aravind L","location":"Online","date":"2020-07-01 to 2020-07-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Expecting some integration testing related concepts were not covered. atleast a generic idea"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All the topics were valuable","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"security & safety related contents were not went in detail also testing part.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Never worked","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW & SWC development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Actually am new to AUTOSAR. Got a good understanding of the concept but I felt a little bit difficulty to understand the details.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1594210329202"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1594210329202"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f05ea4146cc720017abc2d6"},"name":"Gokul VR","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan,Vijayan Thangavel,Swapnil Langarkande,Aravind L","location":"Online","date":"2020-07-01 to 2020-07-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.83","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.83","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.83","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.17","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"But there is some Network issues."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Architecture Explanation and Functionality  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Need More Practical Experience ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"New Experience","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"IVI /ECU Development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"I am satisfied with the training given by Elektrobit on Classic AutoSar. During training, the faculty was able to clear my doubts regarding the Architecture, Code Flow, Configuration Tips followed in the industry and provide real-life examples ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1594223169704"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1594223169704"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f0699f8ac63680017afd1e5"},"name":"Aby Skaria","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan,Vijayan Thangavel,Swapnil Langarkande,Aravind L","location":"Online","date":"2020-07-01 to 2020-07-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Exercise need to improve"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Almost all but need to increase the time schedule","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Bit more explenation about Safety and Security","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes but It was difficult to follow the exercise as the same laptop used for watching and viewing. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1594268152344"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1594268152344"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f0717c9eb1ad20017c55eed"},"name":"Namitha K","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan,Vijayan Thangavel,Swapnil Langarkande,Aravind L","location":"Online","date":"2020-07-01 to 2020-07-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.67","comments":"No presentation taken by Swapnil","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"1"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.17","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.50","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Demo Session"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Both theory and practical","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"Time frame was not enough. In each session, due to the time constraint, most of the theory parts were covered quickly. Also could not cover the Mem stack practical."},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. As a beginner, got a basic idea about Autosar and the EB tresos tool.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1594300361670"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1594300361670"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f17b78db323ef0017a1af82"},"name":"Rajesh AV","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Lokesh Uppara,Kunvar Abhishek Jain,Sivaram Nagarajan,Vijayan Thangavel,Swapnil Langarkande,Aravind L","location":"Online","date":"2020-07-01 to 2020-07-08","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"NA"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":"NA"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"NA"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"The presentation was good","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"NA","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"NA","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"NA","trainerrating":[{"name":"Lokesh Uppara","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kunvar Abhishek Jain","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Vijayan Thangavel","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Aravind L","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The tresos tool usage."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"tresos usage and SWC sample explanation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"creating a SWC sample from the scratch and explanation of generating SWC for any targeted ECU","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"autosar.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":"NA"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"NA"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":"NA"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"NA"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"I have satisfied however, creating new SWC could have given more hands on and experimenting generating SWC for\ntargeted ECU","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595389837433"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595389837433"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2b9bd53797e70017b30378"},"name":"","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"No Comments"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No Comments","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No Comments","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No Comments","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"No Comments","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693461726"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693461726"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2b9c933797e70017b30379"},"name":"","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"He could have covered more about deubugging than scripts part. it was kind of repeated session. he was telling again and again same thing."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"scripting part. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"taking some elf file and code debugging skills than script part. Ex : how to take memory dump, see SFR others stuff could have been explained much more.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For our integration task to debug more application and BSW code. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Thank you for the session. he was more explaining about cmm files then debuggig.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693651990"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693651990"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2b9d333797e70017b3037a"},"name":"","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"4"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"4","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"5","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Development of scripts to automate tasks in Trace32."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Break Points + Flash concepts + Multicore Introduction.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"More on multicore concepts","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1+ years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Regular Integration Activities","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"4"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, I am satisfied with the training. More of such trainings on Scripting , Debuggers and Compilers are helpful for employees to perform their regular activities with more productivity.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693811366"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693811366"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2b9d383797e70017b3037b"},"name":"","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Overview on CMM scripts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"A knowledge on CMM scripts was valuable","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"what all possible controller we all are using can be made list and training would be given on that, for example tc29xx , renesis controller ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For debugging and flashing ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Its really good to have this kind of training. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693816856"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596693816856"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2ba0923797e70017b3037c"},"name":"Pradeep R","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Scripting Using Trace32"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Scripting Using Trace32","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Few More Advance User Interface options if explained would have been better","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"4 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Debugging","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, it was a good learning to us.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596694674781"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596694674781"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2ba8153797e70017b3037d"},"name":"L bhargavi Reddy","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Trainer went through the basics examples which were relatable"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Interaction with participants","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For flashing elf and debugging ( bootloader )","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596696597044"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596696597044"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2bb1de3797e70017b3037e"},"name":"RAVI TEJA SILAPARASETTY","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Debugging the Core and script"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Automating the steps we do in our project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"4yrs","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For Debugging","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, Totally","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596699102538"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596699102538"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2bb2ef3797e70017b3037f"},"name":"","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Scripting"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"approach","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"multicore debugging","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"4yrs","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"BSW configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596699375926"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596699375926"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2cc4e5b7b1ef0017764ccc"},"name":"Ajay Rawat","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"quality was good, used cases were also explained related to others project."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the examples they gave regarding the topics."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands on and the concepts explaination part","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Everything was covered.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"I have not worked with the trace32 but will be working in the upcoming days.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For Flashing the binaries.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes the content of the training was good and was organised in a logical structure and approach.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596769509087"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596769509087"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2cc5fbb7b1ef0017764ccd"},"name":"Kuldeep Miraje","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"the trainer was well experienced and able to solve all queries."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"script writing part","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"debugging","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596769787653"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596769787653"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f30cfca5415650017c614ed"},"name":"Varun S","training":"Trace32","trainers":"Deepak G A","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-08-04","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Deepak G A","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Different Debug methods"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Practice Scripts","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Advance topics ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"10 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Flashing and debugging","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597034442418"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597034442418"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3516d1f865260017e2013d"},"name":"Nagaraj ","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Swapnil Langarkande","location":"Conti online - Aug 2020","date":"2020-08-11 to 2020-08-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"For my Java DSL development work Introduction and Concepts of Autosar  was required, so it meet my expectations. "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Introduction and Concepts of Autosar","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, I am satisfied.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597314769168"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597314769168"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f36281d1852d80017d967ac"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Swapnil Langarkande","location":"Conti online - Aug 2020","date":"2020-08-11 to 2020-08-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":"Some introduction to classic Autosar terminology was needed."},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Overall, it covered most of the important aspects of Autosar and EB Tools"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Introduction to EB Tools and practical exercises","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Some further references where the trainees can build their knowledge further, especially on the OS module. References to OS APIs etc. were missing.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"4 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Development of Swc and Bsw modules","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Overall the training was useful, with some small elements such as \"further reading\" missing.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597384733818"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597384733818"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3cb3f589f2ad0017ac4a0b"},"name":"","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"how the scrum actuallt works"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Interaction with everyone","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"4 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"for planning the tasks for project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes,understood the scrum and its flow with examples iy helped to know many things which were not known to us","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597813749945"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597813749945"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3cc32858bf1000172eb83a"},"name":"Niriksha","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"All the parts covered is useful"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"About the scrum","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All needed were covered.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Four months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For sprint ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597817640401"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597817640401"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3cc43458bf1000172eb83b"},"name":"","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Ineractive session and explaining each component very clearly."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Clearing concepts of each individual.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 yr 5 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For managing the work in Project.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes,  i was satisfied with the training. It was a good learning experience.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597817908959"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597817908959"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3cc5c758bf1000172eb83c"},"name":"Shweta Adarsh Jogur","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"i am new to agile and because of this training i got basic knowledge"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"each content of training was valuable only for me","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"i think necessary topics are covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"new to EB","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597818311757"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597818311757"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3cc6fc58bf1000172eb83d"},"name":"Renuka Pujar","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"1","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"well explained each topic"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597818620393"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597818620393"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3cd43609bdc50017a54a8b"},"name":"","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"The presentation was good, session was iteractive"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Slides","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"none","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Work tracking","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597822006263"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597822006263"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3ce13b09bdc50017a54a8c"},"name":"Maruthi Hanumanthegowda","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Content of the training"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Advantages of Agile over Waterfall model","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Satisfied with the content of the training and presentation. Informative :) .","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597825339084"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597825339084"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3d1c5b9604fd0017929fc2"},"name":"RAVI TEJA SILAPARASETTY","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Sivaram Nagarajan,Ravi Teja Silaparasetty,Swapnil Langarkande","location":"Conti online - Aug 2020","date":"2020-08-11 to 2020-08-13","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sivaram Nagarajan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Ravi Teja Silaparasetty","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Swapnil Langarkande","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Diag, Mode Management, Os"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Os","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"4yrs","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Integration ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Time is not sufficient to deliver all the content. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597840475584"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597840475584"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3e04b985bd390017c07151"},"name":"Madhunita Mahadev","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"understood difference between agile and other methodology (kanban)"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"different roles in agile","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597899961982"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597899961982"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3e05ca85bd390017c07152"},"name":"","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Very Interactive"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Agile, Kanban","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All topics related to this topic covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1.5 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Project","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes  satisfied. It was really knowledgeable and interactive session","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597900234399"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597900234399"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3e0cf385bd390017c07153"},"name":"","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Quiz part was very good."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Advantages of agile over other methodologies , what exactly is agile process were very helpful and were explained good too. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Some quiz kind of self exercises would have been more to get better understanding.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2.5 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Project work","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, overall it was a good learning experience.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597902067804"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597902067804"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3e1632a04ff10017c4b89f"},"name":"Tarun Bagade","training":"Agile Scrum Training","trainers":"Bishnu Prasad","location":"Online (MS teams)","date":"2020-08-17","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Bishnu Prasad","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Video Presentation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Agile","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NOthing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not worked","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"No Task","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597904434856"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597904434856"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f3eb2ef1c4b03001796c5da"},"name":"","training":"Demo Training","trainers":"Mohamed Firdous,Akhil Raju","location":"Test","date":"2020-08-20 to 2020-08-21","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Mohamed Firdous","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Mohamed Firdous","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Mohamed Firdous","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Mohamed Firdous","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Akhil Raju","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"not Applicable"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Valuable part","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"missing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Online training","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"duration and tasks","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Classroom","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Testimonial","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1597944559480"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1597944559480"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f6996c84c23ed00174827c8"},"name":"Pradeep","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ,Kumar, Saran,Goopalliyappa, Manjunathan","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-23","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"Saran and Manjunathan did not take","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kumar, Saran","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Goopalliyappa, Manjunathan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"Saran and Manjunathan did not take","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kumar, Saran","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Goopalliyappa, Manjunathan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.67","comments":"Saran and Manjunathan did not take","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kumar, Saran","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Goopalliyappa, Manjunathan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"Saran and Manjunathan did not take","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kumar, Saran","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Goopalliyappa, Manjunathan","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Most of the 'C' Concepts was kind of re learning again"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Pointers Concept","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All Most all basic were covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands On Session might be less if we are doing online","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"6 months, We use the products for Integration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Both online and Classroom","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600755400584"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600755400584"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f6997544c23ed00174827c9"},"name":"","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ,Kumar, Saran,Goopalliyappa, Manjunathan","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-23","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"Content is good for the known ppl. Can be prepared even for beginners"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"She did a nice presentation","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kumar, Saran","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Goopalliyappa, Manjunathan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}},{"name":"Kumar, Saran","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Goopalliyappa, Manjunathan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.33","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}},{"name":"Kumar, Saran","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Goopalliyappa, Manjunathan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.67","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Kumar, Saran","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}},{"name":"Goopalliyappa, Manjunathan","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Almost yes but i am a very new to this topic, i am unable to understand some topics which is advanced"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Her presentation","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Face to face interaction is missing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Content is good for the topic known ppl. Can be prepared even for beginners","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600755540369"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600755540369"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f6999704c23ed00174827ca"},"name":"Kamia","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"presenatation"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"snippets and excerise","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nothing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"nothing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"1.5 Year","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Online","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756080735"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756080735"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f6999714c23ed00174827cb"},"name":"","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"nil"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"nil","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756081958"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756081958"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f6999764c23ed00174827cc"},"name":"Pradeep R","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Most of the 'C' Concepts was kind of re learning again"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Pointers Concept","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"All Most all basic were covered","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Hands On Session will not be so effective","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"6 months, We use the products for Integration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Both Online and Classroom","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756086586"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756086586"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f69999a4c23ed00174827cd"},"name":"","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"code snippets and use cases "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"pointers and examples","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"link between Autosar arxml and generated code in C, example when P2CONST should be used and when P2VAR etc.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Training Recordings","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"3 months, EB tresos Studio","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Online","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756122579"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756122579"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f6999c94c23ed00174827ce"},"name":"","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"Quality of the content is good for topic known ppl, not for the beginner who is doesn't know about this topic"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"Well done.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Quality of the content is good for topic known ppl, not for the beginner who is doesn't know about this topic"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Usecases for each topic","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"As a beginner i am unable to grab many topics","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Face to face interaction is missing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Classroom","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Quality of the content is good for topic known ppl, not for the beginner who is doesn't know about this topic","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756169041"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756169041"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f699a204c23ed00174827cf"},"name":"","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"2.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"2"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"content could have been explained in much more better way"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"examples","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"basics and many other topics","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"all fine","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"General","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"both","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"I am not satisfied completely as training timing was less and not completed in one go","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756256429"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756256429"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f699a3d4c23ed00174827d0"},"name":"saiprasad","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"pointer concepts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"pointers","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"more regarding endianess","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"its good","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"1.5 yr","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"classroom, more interaction & doubt clarification would be good","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"satisfied","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756285625"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756285625"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f699a494c23ed00174827d1"},"name":"Vipul Singh Rawat","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Content quality can be improved "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Brushing up the old concepts.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"funtion to funtion pointer calling ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Use to of onlne training so no issues.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Classroom ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It brushed up my basic concepts , so yes I am satisfied.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756297671"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756297671"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f699a944c23ed00174827d2"},"name":"Siva Santhosh Javali","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"Good"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":"Good"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":"There is no time to do any Exercises."},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"Good knowledge on topic.","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Duration of training is very limited. These kinda training needs minimum 3 days with ample time to practice coz its being used in actual project."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Content is good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Excersise part","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Not having Interaction with peers is a big Negative during trainings to share or discuss any points.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"3 years. Autosar Integration.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":"Appreciate for planning the Training. Kudos"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":"Mentioned drawbacks earlier."}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Classroom if permitted.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Appreciate the effort during these Covid times but still training should have been more in duration with time to exercise what's been taught. It's an Critical Training topic little bit disappointed. ","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756372389"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756372389"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f699aed4c23ed00174827d3"},"name":"","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"More examples would resolve confusions "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Calm explaination for every question","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Unexpected network issues is a problem","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Classroom","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756460996"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756460996"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f699c494c23ed00174827d4"},"name":"","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"3"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"need more experienced person who is currently working in same domain."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"misra c","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"must have a more experienced trainer.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756809651"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600756809651"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f6c217cad1f1a001751de9b"},"name":"Ajay Mundra","training":"Embedded C","trainers":"Jaladi, Indraja ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-21 to 2020-09-22","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"-"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Jaladi, Indraja ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"content could be more in depth , more practical exercises required"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"bit field","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"MISRA-Rules, Real case scenarios, More intense examples with Bit fields","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Consistency is difficult in online course","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"2","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Any","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Content of the training was not up to the mark","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1600921980540"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1600921980540"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f742f0243d4260017bad269"},"name":"deepak","training":"AR Crypto stack","trainers":"Sharma, Manoj ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-29 to 2020-09-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Hands on session was reply helpful. Things was explained in details"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Theory + Hands on was well explained","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"maybe template of ppt should have been update as contents looked old.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Artifacts required for hands-on session need to be checked if public user has access to contents. It took longer time for access.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"Will be used for future projects.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"No preference","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes :)","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1601449730063"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1601449730063"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f7430e943d4260017bad26a"},"name":"Vipul Singh Rawat","training":"AR Crypto stack","trainers":"Sharma, Manoj ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-29 to 2020-09-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Topics were new to me, so I like the content"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Content and hands on","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"SecOS and few others as mentioned by the trainer ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Still getting used to hand on activity.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"No preference","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes I am satisfied with the training, as every topic was new to me so I can't  judge right now.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1601450217132"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1601450217132"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f74379543d4260017bad26b"},"name":"","training":"AR Crypto stack","trainers":"Sharma, Manoj ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-29 to 2020-09-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"4"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Some expectations were met, not all. Exercise wise, maybe a few more varieties would be helpful."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Understanding the overall picture of the crypto stack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"In detail concepts about the complete stack was missing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"The online training was a bit challenging due to network connectivity and VPN issues","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"NA","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Classroom","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Satisfied, but could have been better, especially the duration of the training. More concepts and details can be covered.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1601451925815"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1601451925815"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f747c85bb842300171d6353"},"name":"","training":"AR Crypto stack","trainers":"Sharma, Manoj ","location":"Bangalore","date":"2020-09-29 to 2020-09-30","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5.00","comments":"","trainerrating":[{"name":"Sharma, Manoj ","rating":{"$numberInt":"5"}}]}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Properly explained"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercise part ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"As per my unnderstanding nothing.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"FOR ONLINE TRAININGS: Which aspects do you consider positive or negative in terms of using the online training format?","question_type":"","answer":"Negative is it challenges Excercise part . ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with the EB product (month or years), for which tasks do you use the product(s)?","question_type":"","answer":"2","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"If you had the choice booking a similar training in the future, which would be your preference (Online, Classroom, No preference)?","question_type":"","answer":"Classroom .","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes .\n","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1601469573572"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1601469573572"}}
